The crew aboard the Quin Zaza
is very diverse.
People who wanted to be in a ship.
People who are on board for certain reasons…
Their origins being different
with their own circumstances.
Everyone here became a draker.
Ah! This is...!
Hey-... Hey!
Everyone, there's an emergency!
Mm?
Like I said, there's an emergency.
This... this is...!
Vanabelle... right?
Wow... It's as if someone drew it
while watching her.
Totally.
There's no way that it'd look that good
without seeing her in the flesh!
Does that mean he saw her like this?
-Nah, there's no way.
-But man...
Either way, this is pretty good…
Ah!
Yeah, not bad at all.
In fact, this is great!
Hey, let me look too!
Ah!
Hey! Stop that!
Let us look at it some more!
Yeah!
It's not as it would wither or anything!
-Denied!
-Eh...
But I wonder who on earth would draw this...
"Catching the wind, seizing the shadows."
So... where are we supposed to go?
♪〜
〜♪
Well, Oken...
With this as a proof...
Can we establish
that there's someone spying on
Vanabelle while she sleeps?
Yeah, there's no other believable option.
We have even 4 women aboard,
which is pretty rare.
I believe that this lucky-
I-I mean, this serious situation
would happen sooner or later!
Either way, who would have thought
that there's someone
so brave as to do that to Vannie!
The room where the drawing was found was...
Jiro, Hiro and Gaga's room.
The culprit is one of those three.
Now this has gotten interesting!
Eh?
Nah, nevermind.
I don't think Jiro-san
would be capable of something like that.
Nope! Sometimes the most
straight-laced ones are the worst!
The engineer's apprentice, Hiro, has
pretty skillful hands too...
Yeah, and he's pretty gloomy,
it could be him.
And Gaga is...
Do you think someone with those looks
would be able to draw?
Well, with those ones as our culprits
it will be pretty easy to find the culprit.
Ooh! How shameful!
So? What are we gonna do?
Yeah, let me see...
First, we get the suspects and...
I see!
Hey, Hiro!
Come here a sec...
Um... Jiro-san!
Can you draw a portrait of me?
What?
It is settled.
Yeah.
The culprit behind this drawing of Vanabelle
it's you, Gaga!
Ah... Wha-!
What are you taking without permission?
To think that you sneaked into the
room of a sleeping beauty...
What a sly bastard.
Huh? What are you talking about?!
Being a bad loser is kinda lame!
Go on, confess your crimes!
Are you the one who drew Vannie-san's portrait?
It's a misun-... misunderstanding!
L-Let go of me!
That hurts!
If you are so worked up about it
it makes you all the more suspicious!
Ow...
I see you are as close as ever...
You see, I can't sleep over here.
And you are quarreling about
something irrelevant again!
Bo-boss...
Wow... I had no idea!
That you were so good at drawing, Gaga-san!
I'm drawing these as a journal of things
that happen in the ship.
Oh! There's a drawing of me!
Are you really able to draw this
only from your imagination?
Yes, I think it's pretty normal...
So that means that you weren't peeping at all.
I'm glad.
Why were you keeping this from all of us?
That... that is because...
Hey, how about you draw me
a nice nude of my type of woman?
Ah, Gaga, one for me too!
I didn't say anything about it
precisely because of this.
Well! From the very beginning I believed
that you, Gaga, wouldn't be
capable of something so low!
Huh?
You suspected him the most!
Oken-san...
With all said and done, I'm glad there isn't
a bad person aboard the ship.
Yeah!
Guys...
Since you are
so energetic and gung-ho...
I will pick a special job for all of you.
Put your back into it!
Originally, Takita, you were the one
who jumped to the wrong conclusions!
Niko-san, weren't you also on board
with the idea from minute one?
When we finish this I'm gonna
have my arms stiff for 2 days straight.
To think that I was off duty today...
My hips hurts so bad!
It will be filthy in no time again anyway!
Why am I doing this too?
Hey!
If you have time for small talk
move those hands instead!
Yes, sir!
If you are so easy on the floor
we are gonna be here till the end of time!
What is this ruckus?
Who knows...
Ah, Vannie-san!
It's... it's nothing.
My hair is unruly as ever...
Doing it by force will make it worse.
Ah, Vannie-san.
Th-thank you very much.
Do you mind dandruff...?
We're all the same inside this ship.
Mmm? What a good smell!
What is that?
It's perfumed oil.
You get this by mixing camellias and dragon incense.
Dragon incense?
It's the mineral obtained from rare secretions
that form inside a dragon's body.
Listen, Takita...
What do you think of this ship?
Eh? Ah, yeah...
I'm completely accustomed to it now!
I'm the type that can sleep anywhere
as long as there's a roof over my head!
I... sometimes feel a bit lost.
I wonder why am I here right now...
And going so far as to kill dragons...
So you do have times of doubt too,
Vannie-san.
You thought I was more aloof?
Ah... no, it's not like that!
Vannie-san, you always have
this cool aura around you.
And your skill catching dragons
is second to no one aboard!
It's not like that...
I just had nowhere to belong to on land.
Nowhere to belong to?
Since I had no place for me to belong to
I became skilled in how to fly.
And that's all.
Ah...
Sorry for letting out something so awkward.
Ah, nevermind.
Ah?
You are always eating bread like that.
I like the way
it soaks in the soup.
U-Um!
We have pickled cabbage!
Don't go only eating
stew and potatoes!
Mika-san! Pass me your plate.
Eh...?
That is so pickled that is
sure to be sour.
It's so fermented precisely
because nobody's eating it!
Takita, I'm committed...
Committed to eat only the
things I like...
Shut up and pass me your plate, please.
Ah! Vannie-san.
Make space for her there.
-No need to mind yourself with that.
-Eh?
Takita!
I left the laundry for you in front
of the boys' quarters.
Eh...? You could do that much
by yourself!
All chores are for the newbies after all.
You left laundry
to do not so much ago!
Hey, Gaga.
You were cleaning the deck
the other day, right?
-What's with that?
-Eh...
Oh... that, yeah.
There's no particular reason...
-My drawings were...
-Drawings?
No... I mean...
Wai-...! Mika-san!
If you are that rough with it
it's gonna end up breaking!
If you don't do this much
it doesn't feel like you've actually done it.
Nooo way!
Let go of the lever, please!
I'm astonished at the passion
you put into doing laundry.
Oh, Vannie-san!
Mika-san is doing this
by brute force!
Let me do it.
I just wanted to help...
-What?
-Nothing...
Mika-san, hang out these instead!
Okay...
By the way, Mika-san...
Didn't you... notice something?
Mmm?
I mean...
Like a good smell coming out or something...
Yeah, a smell clear as day...
Eh!
A very delicious smell...
Oh?
A dragon!
Where... where is it?
It's hidden in the clouds.
I'm going to the lookout to check!
Ah...! Mika-san!
We are going out too.
Nope! We can't see anything from here yet!
You sure it wasn't the shadow of a cloud?
To our 8 o'clock.
It's probably hidden in the clou-
Oh, hey! Mika, wai-!
Crocco!
There's a mountain of clouds to our 8.
It's behind that!
Do us a favour and raise the ship!
Show some respect
to your deputy captain!
He wasn't on the morning shift, was he?
Give us a break and behave!
Mika!
Don't go doing whatever you want!
Hey! Are you listening to me, Mika?
So little space...
Oh!
It looks quite big.
It's the first time I see a dragon so round.
It looks delicious.
Eh?
Ohh! It's pretty huge!
What a strange form...
Okay! All hands on deck! Prepare!
Hurry up!
The dragon waits for no one!
Good one!
As one would expect from you, Gibbs,
you don't miss!
What is it doing?
It is... looking at us.
Wha- What is this?!
Are you alright?
What... was that?
Argh... I'm so dizzy...
Here you go, water.
Ugh... ah, thank you.
What the hell was that?
It was a sound.
It was attacking us with that soundwave.
You mean it wasn't attacking the ship but us?
We won't be able to aim our bomb lances like that.
If this continues, it seems that waiting
for it to grow weaker is the better choice.
Are you listening?
Mmm?
Do you think
we can just wait for it to die like that
for hours on end?
I'm going out to finish it off!
And what are you planning to do?
As long as we have it anchored
it is not a matter if we can stand on it or not!
Don't be stupid!
It's impossible, it'll explode your eardrums!
And we are trying to take its life!
Mika!
Do you have that much fun killing dragons?
Ugh... he is so reckless as ever...
Tell the bridge to
raise our course!
Heh...
It's like... the sky is spinning...
Still screaming, huh?
My head is spinning like crazy...
Get a grip on yourself!
Ah...
Vanabelle...
Are you okay?
Leave me alone! Finish it off!
Quick... put it out of its misery...
Vannie-san!
I... sometimes feel a bit lost.
I wonder why am I here right now...
And going so far as to kill dragons...
So you do have times of doubt too,
Vannie-san.
Since I had nowhere to belong to on land,
I became skilled in how to fly.
Since I had no place for me to
belong to on land...
That's... all there is to it!
It has shrunk quite noticeably...
Great work out there! Are you alright?
Gibbs... I'm participating in the dissection too...
You can't even walk straight.
Good grief...
You're always so careless...
Even if you managed to catch it,
there's no point if you die out there!
I won't die.
I can't allow myself to die,
not until I have savored all of you.
Hunt, dissect and eat.
That's what all drakers are about.
Return peacefully to the clouds
and grant us good winds.
Words for parting.
Eh...
Ah! Mika-san!
Oh, come on! Stay put!
Oh, I found a big rat.
Oh? Ah, it's you Vanabelle.
I'm not snitching food, okay?
Isn't your shift over?
I couldn't sleep, that's all.
What's that?
It's the liver of the dragon we captured today.
I put it in the oiling pot along with its fat.
And secretly cooked it
at a low temperature.
And you don't call that snitching food?
Do you mind accompanying me for a glass?
I see we have some leftovers of
potato and cabbage.
Can you smash these together with a little bit
of oil and salt?
What are we going to make?
Simple countryside cooking.
Spread the pickled cabbage
on a mold coated with oil.
And then press together
liver confit with mashed potatoes.
-Mika.
-Mmm?
When you are hunting dragons
you are always smiling.
It is so much fun?
I wonder.
But... I guess it is fun.
I see...
Yeah...
Then, you press together the ingredients
inside the mold...
And then you remove it with care,
cut it in your desired sized pieces and it's done.
Ohh!!
Will you look at that beauty!
Yeah! It's so good!
Vanabelle, this is great!
It's strong, rich and fresh at the same time!
It seems like we randomly put this together
but it tastes like proper cooking!
Oh? What are you eating there?
It's not as if I was snitching food!
It's something that Vanabelle made.
I was not asking you that.
Back from your shift?
Yeah, I'm freezing all over.
Now's our turn to work.
Both of you here and alone?
-What a rare sight.
-Indeed.
This looks good, don't mind if I do...
Ah! Wai-!
Yeah! This is great!
Eh? Well, if it's so good...
Ahh! Those were all for me...
Mmm... it's delicious!
Vannie!
Please make this again some other time!
Yeah... if you are happy with something like that.
Here you go.
Ah! Thanks for the food!
Listen, Mika.
Why are you here?
On this ship?
Isn't it obvious?
It's because I love dragons.
Hunting dragons, dissecting them
and eating them...
And the way we all live here.
But above all else, it's because
I get to eat a lot of dragons here.
If you want something good,
there are many other tasty things out there.
But dragons are the most delicious of all.
Ugh...
So cruel!
Jiro-san told me!
You were all eating
something tasty yesterday!
Ah?
You're so unfair!
Can you not yell next to my ear?
Unfair! Unfair!
Why didn't you wake me up?
Ah, Jiro-san, this goes for you too!
All of you excluding me...
Vannie-san, don't laugh
and tell them off too!
♪〜
Translation: TomoyaNC   Proofreading: akemilena