Right now, I'm working hard
to become a full-fledged draker.
I need to learn a lot of
new things every day, though...
Close your arms more.
Okay, focus.
You don't need to hold your breath.
Yes, that's good.
I can't let you shoot real bullets just yet,
but keep practicing every day.
Yes!
It's coming!
Fire!!
Yes, on point!
It seems we don't need more, right?
Yeah. Well, aren't you starting to
look the part!
I can't be a newbie forever!
Nah,
you still have a long way to go.
Ah... Mika-san?
Takita.
Tell the bridge to bring the ship closer.
We'll get good oil from this one.
Probably.
Please don't jump on it again, okay?!
Ahh!!
Geez!
Man, why does he always...
Draking vessel, Quin Zaza.
This is the place I belong to now.
♪〜
〜♪
Jiro, can you fit some more there?
Yeah, it's fine.
Come over here too.
Yes!
So hot...
Just a bit more!
-Tired?
-Eh?
Of course we are!
We've been extracting oil for
48 hours straight!
I'm dead tired...
It's hot, smelly and we're covered in soot!
Takita, what a place you've ended up in!
You bet...
But you always look like you're having fun.
Oh, to be young...
Eh?
We'll arrive to a big town in a bit.
When we deliver all this oil to the
refinery company over there
we'll be able to relax for a while.
One last effort!
Yeeeeah...
If we sell all this,
how much will it be?
We got a lot of good oil this time, so...
Gibbs-san, excuse me...
Oh, Lee-san.
How much do you think it will be?
Eh? Ah...
Are dragons that valuable?!
"One dragon makes seven towns flourish",
they say.
Meat and oil go without saying,
but depending on the species, the bones
can become craft products,
and entrails can be materials for medicines.
Dragons are mountains of treasures.
And on the other hand,
the loss when we fail to capture one
is huge, too.
Draking vessels are a money hole.
Actually, even with this, we're in the red.
U-um...
By the way, how much would...
my compensation be...?
Hmm, let's see...
Only... that...
Takita-san, since you still owe your entrance
pay to the ship,
that's what's being substracted.
You have it hard too, huh.
I know it's obvious, but was there
still that much left?
I gotta work hard to pay it off!
Takita, give me some oil cake.
What are you going to do with that?
If you dry and dehidratate it,
you can get some good broth from it.
And you can simply boil it and
eat it like that.
Ah?
You have it hard too, Mika-san...
The wind feels so good!
Is that a passenger ship?
The town must be close...
It sure gets cold really fast outside!
Eh?
That scared me! A bird?
No, birds shouldn't fly this high...
Eh?
Don't tell me... it's...
Could this be a...?
Wait!
Ahhh... we're finally done.
Today was so hard...
-Yeah...
-I'm so tired!
Hey, what are you gonna do when we land?
Goes without saying!
Booze, of course!
The sky has dragons! The land has booze!
Ah!
Guys! A small one has sneaked
into the ship...
What? Takita, leave it for later.
We're worn out...
Yeah, yeah! You rest too, Takita.
Eh? Um... Wait!
Okay!
Dragons are a mountain of treasures!
Hey, Takita.
Hmm?
What is she doing?
Where did it go...?
What are you doing?
Ah, no, this is nothing...
More importantly, why are you
following me?
No particular reason...
Mika-san, are you snitching food again?
Indeed.
"Indeed" you say...
Gibbs-san!
Look at this bite.
You were attacked? What bit you?
It wasn't a mouse, that's for sure.
It was bigger.
Like a dog or a cat?
No, it was something different.
I heard Gibbs collapsed!
What happened?
Apparently he got bit by something weird
and collapsed.
Something weird? Like what?
Hm? Takita?
U-um...
That could be...
You haven't found it yet?!
I'm so sorry!
We are searching everywhere
on the ship but...
Damn it, what are you doing?!
Don't tell me... it escaped outside...
You need to find it no matter what!
It's incomparable to any bird or beast
around there!
Hey, explain what happened.
You know something, don't you?
Did you do something again?
Hey, what's with the ruckus?
Ah, Vannie.
What happened?
-Gibbs collapsed, apparently.
-Eh?
Eh? It's Takita.
A small dragon?
And you say it ran inside the ship?
Um... it stopped on the deck's handrail...
And when I noticed, it had jumped inside...
And you let it go?
Why didn't you tell us immediately?
Because everyone was so tired...
And I thought "I can deal with this myself!"
And you say it's venomous?
I've never heard of a dragon like that.
I bet you wanted to catch it alone and
get a good chunk of money, right?
I may or may not...
Takita, was it about this size?
Eh? Ah, no...
About this... I think.
Really!
I've never seen a dragon this small!
How about we split in groups and catch it?
-Yeah!
-I agree!
I'll go tell the others!
-No...
-What?
It has either poison or a virus...
If we're not careful and end up
with more people infected, it'd be for nothing.
Wh-What should we do...
Until we solve it,
we should gather all in one place
and select a few people to catch it.
Hm... it's as Jiro says.
Now, who should go...
Well, he's already in.
Ah! I'll go too!
Mika-san, wait!
Mika-san!!
I can't rest assured with just those two...
I'll go too.
If it's small we don't need strength.
And you have good eyes.
-Can we leave it to you?
-Sure.
So...
Why did it have to be like this?
The bridge is in the furthest end
of the ship...
Well, nothing we can do for now.
Ah!
Berko! That's unfair!
Ah? It's my lifeline!
How long it's been since we took her in?
About three months, I'd say.
Thing sure aren't boring since Takita arrived.
Right.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Mika-san, do you smell any dragon?
The smell of dragon oil is adhered
to the ship and my body
and that's the only thing I smell.
I suddenly want some fried food.
It's not here either...
Are you sure you didn't mistake it, Takita?
It's real!
Gibbs-san was actually attacked!
Normally, dragons don't get close to ships
on their own.
Eh?
Then, why?
Was it attracted by something...?
That's probably this smell.
What?
Dragon oil...
It might be
that it gets closer to dragons
bigger than it relying on their smell
and parasitizes on them to live.
There's a lot of different dragons, huh...
The dragons we know are just a small part.
Takita!
You little...!
Huh?
Ugh, this guy...!
Wait!
Here!
I'm telling you to wait!
Dammit!
You jerk!
-Oops...
-Wait!
-This little...
Got it!
Nice! Don't let it go!
If it bites, the poison will...!
You... you saved me...
So this is the one that bit Gibbs.
It's the first time I see such a small one.
Mika, are you really going to eat it?
We still don't know if it's venomous.
Don't come crying if you get poisoned.
It'll be fine as long as I don't eat the entrails.
Man...
Well, we were lucky we could solve it this time.
Yeah...
Newbie, don't go off on your own too much.
So cruel! You're a newcomer too, Jiro-san!
I'm a full-fledged crew member already.
Don't lump me with someone who joined
for no particular reason.
Oh? You've learned to talk big, eh, Jiro?
H-hey, Niko!
What the hell...
Um...
Are you really going to eat it?
What else is there to do?
Um... if we sold it in a town,
maybe we'd get some money...
We can't even extract oil from one so small,
so I don't think it will be worth too much.
Is that so...
Yoshi-san! I want to eat cutlet.
I can't make cutlet.
-We've run out of eggs.
-Eh?!
Then what should I do with my life?!
About what?
Cutlet isn't possible, but...
Yeah, it seems the skin is edible too.
How about we make it "demon style"?
Demon style?
Yeah. There are various theories about
the origin of its name, but
its appearence when it's finished
looks like a demon,
and apparently that's where
the name comes from.
It doesn't feel like I'm cooking a dragon.
Even though it's small,
it does have a proper heart.
Dragons fly on the sky thanks to this.
Ohh, with this...
After beheading it and emptying it out,
we slice it down its back.
Mika, do it, I'll prepare the marinade.
Sure.
How skillful...
It's just small, but it's the same as
dissecting any other dragon.
Olive oil, lemon, salt and pepper,
and then, some spices I found in the galley,
and we leave it for 30 minutes.
This'll do.
On a frypan with a generous amount of oil,
we fry it with the skin side down.
Irresistible!
Press it down with a pot full of water,
and when it gets a good fried colour,
flip it and repeat the process.
Put the skin side down again,
and when it's crispy fried...
It's done.
Okay! Time to eat...
It's hot!!
Hey, Mika! Don't tell me...
-Mika-san!
-It had poison after all...!
So good!!
Geez! Don't scare us like that.
Here.
We caught it ourselves.
This is delicious!
The outside is crispy and aromatic,
and the inside is so tender
the umami just goes whaam!
Glad to hear.
Oh, let me see...
What the hell, stingy.
To begin with, you are too much
of a glutton always!
That's not true!
I really can't let myself
be blinded by greed...
I've never been blinded by it so
I don't understand.
I can't really agree with that.
Ah, right!
Let's bring Gibbs-san half of this.
Mika, aren't you too blinded by greed
after all?!
Not at all.
Ah... don't take it!
No!
Wait! Stop!!
You still haven't found the dragon?!
That's a gift for the royal family!
It's a really rare ultra-small type
that can be appreciated even indoors!
It's worth 2 billions! 2 billions!
Do whatever you need to find it!
I don't think there's any poison, though...
Headache, chills, shivers, and fever.
These symptoms are just a cold.
Right.
His exhaustion might caught up to him.
Gibbs-san has been working day and night
with barely no relief.
Ah!
Gibbs works too hard!
Oh! So good.
And you too...
Eh?
Don't try too hard either, okay...
Ah, no!
I have a huge debt to pay off,
so I have to!
Ah, by the way,
why are you in the ship, Jiro-san?
Eh? Ah...
For a lot of reasons.
A lot, huh...
Right! I see, I see.
Well, yeah.
A lot.
But it's not good to keep secrets!
That's...
Well, isn't it good that it's lively?
♪〜
〜♪