It's only after arriving to a big city,
that drakers can finally stretch
their legs.
Just for a brief moment...
That's precisely why,
it becomes an irreplaceable memory.
I'm sorry to impose on you
for dinner as well...
Mika-san, we have to get going.
Heeey.
Geez...
I'm sorry again, he always sleeps
as soon as he drinks...
He's always so sloppy.
I see he hasn't changed.
That's what happens when he drinks
with Gramps Ura.
He's stupidly strong with alcohol.
Nanami-san...
Is the Quin Zaza leaving soon?
There's still repairs to do so
I think we'll stay for a while.
I can't eat anymore...
Then you'll be able to see the
festival the day after tomorrow.
Isn't that great?
Eh, there's a festival?!
Did something happen?
What's going on?
Hey, that... it's smoke!
What?
Is that... a fire?
That way's the port.
Ah, Mika-san!
-Takita, let's go.
-Ah, yes!
Shit, what's going on?!
Hey, this is bad...
It's coming this way!
♪〜
〜♪
Tsk... and we just got here today.
Ah, Crocco-san!
Where are the others?
There was a call for rescue,
they're on their way.
What do we do with the Zaza?
Uh...
Mayne, you go wake up the old man Dag
and warm up the engine.
Yes.
Capella, go to the bridge.
Make it so we can move it at any given time.
Okay!
Guess we gotta save the vacation for later.
Well...
Look what have you done!
It's a huge loss!
E... evacuate!
Hurry up! Run away!
Hey, there's someone hurt!
Shit, what way do we run to?!
Hey! What's going on?
Isn't that your ship?
Y-you guys...
Here, I'll lend you a hand.
Hang in there.
Ugh... thanks...
You didn't finish it off?
That's impossible.
We've taken down dragons that big
countless times before!
It suddenly started moving when
we got back to the ship!
What?
I guess there are dragons out there
much tougher than we think.
We didn't use enough for it to be lethal?
No way... we used a whole lot of poison.
Poison?
In our ship we shoot poison
to capture dragons.
For that dragon too, we let it
fall to the ground and towed it after that.
That's way too violent!
The hell I care.
Well, don't mind the details now,
helping people comes first.
Hurry up, before the dragon
starts rampaging!
Yeah!
Vannie! Let me.
Oh, man...
He would've been happier if he
kicked the bucket just like that...
When my time comes please
do it to me, Vannie.
Hey! We need help over here too!
Coming!
Ready, and...
Go!
Hang in there!
Why is there a dragon inside the city...?
Ah... and it's so...
It's...
Huge!
It's gonna charge into the city!
Run, Takita!
Ah, Mika-san!
It's so angry...
No...
Ah! It's scared?
Everyone, get out of here!
City guards!
Eh?
Don't let it get any closer
to the town areas!
Evacuate, quickly!
This thing...
Idiot! Don't shoot at random!
G... good! Kill it!
Yes, sir!
It's working!
Keep shooting!
Stop!
What's that...?
Don't care, attack it!
What's it doing?
Run! Quick!
What's that?
The city is... on fire!
W-what was that?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know...
Mika! Takita!
So you were here.
Evacuate the citizens outside the port!
Gibbs-san!
You okay?
Yes, somehow.
We need to evacuate too, quickly.
Mika!
Yeah, it's the first time I see
one like that.
Did something good happen?
Ah, no, not really...
You look like you got your heart stolen.
Did you find a good man?
It's not like that.
I hope you understand, though.
Whimsical dreams will be your demise.
Yes, I know.
Hey, girls!
We're evacuating, come!
And where are we supposed to evacuate to?
Outside the city!
What happened?
They said a dragon is on a rampage.
No matter if this place goes down,
it will be the same everywhere else.
We don't have anywhere to go to.
What are the drakers doing?
Apparently it's precisely their ship
that they can't use.
Good grief...
and the mess they did today too...
Because of them,
we can't do business in peace!
Anyway, I'll be going on ahead.
You take refuge soon too!
No festival for us, huh?
Ah... the merchant ships are all gone too.
We should get going as well!
I'm back!
Takita! Where were you?
Come on, we're getting out of here.
Eh, no way...
Then what's going to happen
to the people of this city?
Ah... that's...
That dragon has stopped moving
for now, but...
What are you going to do if we get
involved in its frenzy?
We're gonna end up like that big ship!
You saw that heat ray and blast,
didn't you, Takita?
Yes...
First of all, we couldn't possibly
do anything with a dragon that huge...
But...
Gibbs-san!
Huh? Mika isn't with you?
Eh?
He was with us until a moment ago...
That jerk... what's he thinking?!
He can only be thinking about one thing.
What an idiot!
Jiro, I'm sorry but could you
get Mika...
Jiro?
Gibbs.
Can't we take the townspeople on board
the Quin Zaza?
Take them on board for what?
Jiro, I undersand how you feel, but...
Ah, come on, we can't stay here
wasting time, right?
I...
It can't fly anymore.
Gramps Ura.
They used poison, apparently.
Indeed. I can tell from the smell.
And to make it worse,
it lost its sight.
That's why it's scared.
Mika, boy.
Do you know what's
deeper than the sky?
It's people's...
That's fine and all, but
can we eat it?
What?
Gibbs! We can carry the people to
the neighbouring town.
We're about the only ship that's left here.
Then...!
Not realistic, I have to say.
Eh?
You say "the neighbouring town"
but it's still pretty far away.
How many round trips do you plan to do?
To begin with, this is
a problem between that ship that brought
a half-dead dragon and this city.
We have nothing to do with this.
You're not being your usual self.
Heeey!
Ah, Mika!
What have you been-
Everyone, get ready!
We can eat that dragon!
Right! So happy!
Eh... Yes!
E-eh?
Ah... you're one of a kind...
We were just talking about
getting out of here...
Eh, why?!
It was people's actions that hurt
the dragon to that extent.
Ah, grandpa!
Then, it should also be people's
actions that put an end to it.
Originally, humans and nature...
So, we can extract the poison
from its meat
and eat it, right?
Yes...
It depends on the type of poison, but
there is always a method.
He says we can eat that huge thing!
Hear it?
Don't "hear it?" us!
Eat it?
I... think it's fine if
we capture it.
Huh?
Vannie-san!
Even if we had encountered
something that big in the sky,
we wouldn't have been able to touch it.
But now, it's different.
It's a wounded dragon,
which has fallen to land.
Like we said earlier, we're outsiders.
If we fail,
no one will put the blame on us.
If it goes wrong,
we can just run away.
If it goes well, the benefits
are for us.
Especially, for a poor ship like ours,
the only chance to catch something this big
is now. Never again.
Vannie...
Hey, who are you calling a poor ship?
Gibbs.
Think of a way to catch that dragon.
Eh, for real?
Huh? Are we doing it, Crocco-san?
Now that's come to this,
what else we gotta do?
Great! Leave it to me.
We might be poor but we have
experience and intuition going for us!
We'll teach the rest of the ship crews
a lesson or two!
One last big catch before our vacation!
Let's do this.
We're drakers!
I came to an agreement with
the other ship's captain.
He's going to lend us some people.
Here's the memorandum.
Did he give you trouble?
The captain's a calm person.
The crew didn't seem satisfied though.
Who was the one who packed these?
Ah, that would be me.
This is wrong!
If you don't put the
bullets and gunpowder in pairs,
we can't use them right away!
'ight...
But man, we're just going to attack it
both from land and the air at the same time.
Can you call that a strategy?
Come on... sure that's not
experience nor intuition.
Well, things will go however they go.
And if they go wrong, that'd be bad.
Ah... if that happens
say goodbye to the business.
As long as we are alive...
You three!
If you have time to talk,
move your hands instead!
Takita!
You'll be the one loading the guns, okay?
Make sure to know what's in the cart!
-Yeees.
-Hey, Mika!
Ah? What.
Nothing!
We don't know when will the dragon
start rampaging again!
Everyone, hurry up!
Jiro-san is very enthusiastic today.
What the hell's with him?
I loaded the harpoon gun with
double the gunpowder.
It should do quite a lot of damage
if it explodes inside the dragon!
Wow, you splurged there.
I won't forgive you if you fail.
You take care of the ship!
Make it work, okay?
Leave it to me!
Gibbs! We're almost done preparing.
Let's go over the plan again...
What's that?
An autogyro! How rare!
The guys from the other ship?
Those guys... what do they intend to do?
Oh, no!
Good thing this didn't burn.
Right!
That's our prey, to begin with.
To think he accepted their proposal...
Our captain's not right in the head!
Yeah.
As if I could let them take
300 barrels of dragon oil from
under our noses!
We'll finish it off.
Did it work?
Those jerks!
What have they done...
It's about to go wild...
It was all for nothing!
No way!
That's dangerous!
Those idiots! They ran off on their own!
We're starting as soon as possible!
Tell those down there!
H-hey, Jiro!
I'm on a hurry, please make way!
It's falling!
Oh, no...
This is bad! Really bad!
Katja!!
♪〜
Translation: akemilena   Proofreading: TomoyaNC