Wow!
There's a city inside the crater!
That's the city of Quon.
A flourishing port city famous for being
a base for drakers.
Since we have lot of repairing to do
we'll be stationed in this city for a while.
-Yahoo!
-Good grief...
Ahh...! Landing at last.
We had a lot of trouble with the
air pirates and everything after all.
Jiro, this is your first time in
this city, right?
Yeah.
This city is a rendezvous point
for a lot of other draking vessels, isn't it?
So diligent as ever!
Our Jiro will be Jiro wherever
he goes, eh?
Wha- What's your problem?
It's just that you all are too easy-going.
Mika-san, there! Look, look!
Already lookin'.
Let's land quickly and begin dissecting.
You're no fun...
Mika-san, how can you be so dull?
Even after landing
There's plenty of work for
drakers to keep our hands busy.
But, certainly, going to a new place
sure gets your heart racing.
♪〜
〜♪
Hey! Let's begin!
Yeah!
Hey, Takita!
Come over here,
let's see you try your hands at dissecting.
Eh?
You can't stay "the newbie"
forever, you know.
Ye-... yes, sir!
First, try an horizontal cut
in the direction of the tail from there.
Understood!
Put more strength into it!
Don't be a scaredy cat!
Do it in one go! Now!
Ye-... yes!
Wow...
Okay... here goes!
Drive your blade between the meat and the
skin to cut it away.
So tough...
A little more! Go!
Okay, Takita.
That was pretty good for your first time.
Let's go for the red meat now.
Ye- yes, sir!
At long last!
We're done with all the dissecting
and deliveries!
Finished the clean up too!
Let's eat something tasty
and hit the nearest tavern!
Yeah!
Jiro...
You're coming with us!
The sensation from the dissection is
still in my hands.
We've sure come a long way...
It's done, it's done!
What's with her?
If you take into account that she
was still not used to living aboard...
Dealt with not only a storm
but air pirates shooting at her as well...
You'd be pretty overwhelmed
by all of that, don't you think?
That girl...
She doesn't let her show in her face...
But I'm pretty sure that she's been pretty tense.
And now that tension has gone off all at once.
Are you sure she's not just hungry?
It's during moments like this that
newbies decide to leave the ship.
Eehh!
Mmm?
Here.
Eh?
So tasty!
You can tell it's different from
meat roasted in a normal skewer!
Yeah, this is roasted after being
marinated in wine.
I was hoping to have these marinate
overnight but oh well...
Oh, that's why I thought I smelled
something tasty!
The skewers are made from grapevine wood.
If you roast meat using these
some of its aroma ends within it.
Mika-san, aren't you going out
somewhere today?
I'll go once I'm done
eating these.
Just... wait a moment, please!
Mmm?
Why did you go all-out and changed
your clothes?
A young lady doesn't have the chance
to visit a city everyday!
If this isn't the moment to wear
my fanciest clothes, then, when is it?
How about this, young man?
-Wahh!
-Don't need any.
Please, come again!
I didn't know you smoked.
Grrrr!
Hey... I'm gonna leave you here.
Ugh... fine...
Mika-san...
Where are we going?
We'll arrive soon.
A tent?
Oh my.
That smell...
I'm glad...
that you didn't kick the bucket yet.
Gramps Ura.
Ha... I'm also glad you didn't too,
Mika.
I didn't see you here
for a month or so.
Nope, it's been 2 or 3 years, gramps.
Oh my? Do you have a companion
with you today?
I wonder if it is a young lady.
Mister, your eyes...
Oh?
How did you know I was
a young lady?
I can tell by the smell.
See? Spot on!
You're too innocent.
What's with this old pervert?
The Thousand Heads Hunter.
He is the chief of the clan
that passes down their wisdom
on how to hunt dragons and dissect them.
But now I'm a simple senile
old fool, as you can see.
Besides that, he always takes
care of these.
What are those?
They're dragon pelts.
From the dragons we hunted.
Ohh... it is pretty well tanned.
What will be they used for?
To make one of these.
This tent...?
It is an ancient tradition...
We sew the pelts of the dragons we dissected
for the new generations to inherit.
Each pattern is different and all of them
share the same meaning: a dragon hunted.
Eh?
This is the first dragon I hunted.
E-... eh?
Which... means that...
All of these patterns
represent dragons?
Here... it is starting to tear...
That one was from 3 generations
before Gramps Ura.
I'm... I'm touching an ancient dragon...
That was a dragon hunted by
a famous dissection expert named Ino.
This one was so big that they
had to call people from the neighbouring town.
And even after that,
it took seven whole days to dissect.
Wow...
But how do you know about all
of them, Mika-san?
Gramps Ura told me all the stories
and they got stuck in my head.
Mika used to sit there in front of
that wall without moving for days.
I think I can understand why he did that.
Since we have this pelt
from our most recent dissection...
Please, tan it well.
That one! That was from the very
first dragon I dissected!
Will it form part of this
wall too?
Umm... I see, I see...
In that case,
I think it deserves a very special spot.
Come here, Nanami!
The pelt teaches you the way
its pattern is gonna be.
Ohhh...
Its colour, feel, scales and hair...
Its irregularities and scars...
You can use all that to form
an expression of the pattern by instinct.
I see...
-Wanna try?
-Ah!
Of course!
Insert the needle and sew
both sides with the thread while pulling it.
Be careful the needle doesn't get
stuck with the thread.
"Dragon's skin tapestry"
It's... It's done!
The stitching is a bit rough
and it is a little twisted but...
I really like it.
I'm moved!
Ah... What's that?
That Vanabelle...
She was just hungry
as I thought!
Yes, that's it.
Wahh... what a beautiful colour.
How does it look?
Good old Dag is checking
it right now.
The structure and joints seem fine
so it seems we only need to replace the plating.
That's the silver lining, huh?
Although...
The gains we got this time
have almost vanished after
the necessary expenses and repair costs.
My head hurts so bad...
Where are all the others?
Everyone disappeared into
the city quite a while ago.
Damn, what a bunch of slackers.
Well, well, don't you prefer it this
way instead?
Yeah, we don't have our noisy Takita
around after all.
That's without question.
Sometimes it is nice to have a drink
between only us grown-ups.
Oh, you in?
I have something special for this ocassion!
Wow, look at that, amazing...
They got a huge one.
Ah... a vessel from the guild?
You can feel the difference in funds
in your bones.
Ah... I wish our ship was as big as
that one...
Yeah...
The value of a ship isn't
measured by its size!
Ouch...
I'm going back to the captain's cabin!
You both know that you can't badmouth
our Quin Zaza in front of him.
If I could, I'd like to dock the Zaza
and overhaul its engine and stuff, you know?
The frontal aileron tends to give me problems
lately too...
I wonder if its chain has become loose.
I'd like to check the steering system
thoroughly to...
Ah... why this again...
We finally got some time off and
we can't stop talking about work.
With our lifestyle, there's not many
interesting things to talk about...
Vannie... how about you?
Eh? How about what?
"What?", don't play dumb!
Being as popular as you are,
you're sure to have plenty of partners to choose from!
Umm... not particularly.
Seems like she's not really interested in this...
To the point it's actually endearing.
Excuse me...
This round is a treat from the clients
over there...
Mmm?
Ahhh... not my type at all...
They seem like trouble...
We'd rather not, thanks.
Ahh...
Huh...? What the fuck's your problem?!
Our drinks are as good as any other!
Yeah, that's it!
I don't drink anything I haven't paid
for myself.
Huh... we have an stuck-up lady right here.
Annoying men aren't precisely
popular anywhere, you know?
But I like my women feisty like you.
They're at it again...
Wait, wait, don't make a man
lose face like that.
If you want to have a drinking contest
I wouldn't mind to oblige.
Mmm?
About the loser's penalty,
let's see...
How about paying for all the rounds
of everyone present in this lovely tavern?
Tsk...
Seems like you have the guts, eh?
We accept the challenge!
-Ahhh...
-That's our girl!
Vannie-san...
Will you be ok after saying that?
Phew! I'm falling for you!
Eh...? You are, like,
pretty amazing.
You're noticing that now?
Yeah!
Say, why are you working in this kind
of place?
-Hey! Come over here!
-Right away!
What is that long face for, eh?
Niko...
If you find any girl to your liking
don't be shy and invite her to a room!
Ah... nah, I'm good.
I'm just here because you guys dragged me.
Besides that...
I can see from a mile away that if I did
anything I'd end up becoming the butt of the joke.
You know I think of you as you
were my cute little brother...
But man, rubble like us...
You can't say when we will
have another chance like this.
Let go of me, brute!
Please, put her down! That girl
isn't taking any customers yet!
No way, I want her and her alone.
Wait, you! What are you misunderstanding?
Let me go!
She will end up taking customers
sooner or later.
If that day is today, it doesn't
matter, right?
That uniform... he is a member
of a ship crew too.
Jiro, leave them alone.
It's better if we don't put ourselves in troubl-
Hey, you! Put her down!
-Oh...
-Can't you see that she dislikes it?
You... are you a draker?
Yeah. We just hunted a huge
dragon too.
As a draker, too, I'd rather not
see something that does our name dirty.
But this place is precisely where
things get pretty dirty, boy.
Can't you put me down before your
little conversation?
Ow...
-Quick, go upstairs and...
-Eh?!
This little pipsqueak says he's a draker!
It's because of people like you that
drakers get scorned everywhere!
What?
-Mmm?
-Ah?
Ow...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry...
You see, I can't find my footing sometimes...
Niko!
Would you be so kind
as to not pick on my little brother?
Huh??
Are you picking a fight with us?
What seems to be the problem?
Can't take it easy like this.
If you are going to fight,
do it outside!
They're gonna fight, yeah!
You see, I can't control
my hands too sometimes...
Heh, how amusing.
Ah... what the hell were they thinking?
You sure you don't need to go?
I'll pass.
I'm a firm pacifist.
Stop that...
Ah... This has become a whole mess...
Ah... my precious bar...
-Now's our chance!
-Oh? Hey!
Wait!
This lady is amazing!
I... I give up.
That's our Vannie!
She drank everything without
breaking a sweat!
The stalls are already in place!
The day after tomorrow,
there's going to be an annual festival.
You! What's your name?
I'm Jiro.
My name's Katja.
Thank you for earlier.
All that running made me hungry!
"Dragon meat hand-rolled Laghman"
I like mine with plenty of
smashed peanuts!
Boss, can we eat this over there?
Yeah, as long as you return the plate.
Okay!
What's this? It's delicious!
You were right, the more peanuts,
the better!
Right? Enjoy it thoroughly.
I say that, but you were the
one who paid for it.
Eh... so you guys travel around the
world searching for dragons...
Maybe this meat is from one of the
dragons you caught, eh, Jiro?
Hey! Tell me stories about the sky!
My father was a draker as well...
And when I was a kid, he used to
tell me a lot of stories.
I see, I see!
So, in our ship there's this guy
named Mika who is amazing!
But, when I'm not there to look after
him, he always end up doing something reckless!
That sounds crazy!
Oh, wait a moment...
-Here!
-Thank you!
It sounds nice...
Waking up and being over the clouds...
Well, life in the sky isn't so easy...
I've never set a foot out of this
city in all my life.
Since they sold me when I was little
I've been here, always.
Isn't it ridiculous?
Even though we're in a port city,
I've never been to anywhere else.
It's time I go back...
Thanks for accompanying me.
I only ever saw the festival
from my window.
It was pretty fun to have
a little taste of it!
Oh...
Well, see you later!
Listen!
The day after tomorrow...
Let's come here together!
Bye-bye.
Guys, I'm beyond tired of this bullshit!
Each and every one of you, what the
fuck were you thinking, bunch of brainless monkeys?
I hope the brainless monkeys reflect
on what they did.
Soraya...
You were there and did nothing to stop them,
you're just as guilty!
Eh! No way in hell!
Hey, Jiro! Where have you been?
To begin with, this was all because you did...
Yeah...
Ah? What's his problem?
What happened, guys?
You look totally wrecked.
These are our proud medals as men.
Woah... it looks painful.
Is this seat free?
Ah... Vannie...
You've been out heavy drinking again, right?
Just a tiny bit.
And that's why I need to cool off.
-Vannie...
-Yeah?
Listen, I...
Nevermind...
That ship is...!
How the hell is that dragon moving
in the dissection dock?!
♪〜
Translation: TomoyaNC   Proofreading: akemilena