Seems that the engine is working well
after being repaired in Quon city.
Yeah.
It's doing its work in moving us
away from civilization.
Where are my dear bustling
sounds of the city...?
We are again immersed in the sounds
of rowdy men in a crowded space.
There you go again...
Wanna quit?
As if.
It's not as if someone is waiting
for me on land anyway.
Ah... mmm, I see.
Oh, Jiro...
Oh... you seem pretty pumped-up!
Jiro, you got a haircut, huh?
It doesn't matter, right?
It was bothersome anyway.
It looks good on you!
Eh... thanks...
Mika-san, there you go snitching
food again...
Gimme some too! Gimme!
What are you looking at?
The smell of the wind has changed.
The smell?
Yeah.
We're gonna catch the westerly winds
and look for dragon shadows.
Well... from here on out
this is uncharted territory for us as well.
Eh... could it mean...
danger?
Has it been a single moment aboard
when we're not exposed to danger?
You have a point.
Also, you boarded in the best
possible moment, Takita.
Eh... eh?!
From this moment on, this ship
will proceed, as planned,
to aim for "the dragon corridor".
The possibilities to encounter
a pod are next to zero...
And, in the case we do,
it'll be a difficult hunt,
but with our ears and eyes
I can assure you that we'll manage!
If it goes well, we'll make
a quick buck!
Our time has come.
How many years do you think
we've been preparing for this?
Indeed. And I beg of you to be
successful in this.
Don't forget the big
investment that went into
making this hunt possible
in the first place.
Once we are done with this,
this time we're gonna have our break for real!
Ah... what a beautiful sound...
Please, continue being in a
good mood for me!
Ahh... draking at this high altitude...
I hope our hull lasts enough.
It's a duel to see who falls apart first:
the ship or us!
So scary...
"The dragon corridor"
The course of the Quin Zaza is now
directed to that special place.
They said that it's a dangerous zone
but, instead of cowering, everyone
seems to be in high spirits.
As for me... I couldn't
really decide at the time.
♪〜
〜♪
Ah... Capella.
You may be short sighted
but your skills are the real deal.
"Short sighted"? That's uncalled for!
We're counting on you!
Ah... Understood.
So creppy...
Bridge... don't fail us.
Why are we coursing between cliffs
even though we're an airship?
We are looking for updrafts.
When we find one, we'll go up
in no time.
Ah... are there dragon pods
above the cliffs?
Yes, above these thick clouds.
There should be a migrating pod,
a "ferry", that only goes through here
during this season.
"Should"? That doesn't sound
very reassuring...
Ah... no, I mean...
Well, we don't have other option but to
believe in Crocco-san's calculations and intuition.
It's not as if we came here
with no plan at all.
Ah... at least we're in better hands
than relying on Gibbs' intuition.
Mmm? Mika-san?
I can't wait.
Ahh... that means we
are on the right trail.
We caught the updraft!
Any obstacles?
Okay, Capella, raise our bow!
Yes!
Engine room! Full speed ahead!
Ah! At long last!
Maximum output, here we go!
Geez... you're too into this!
Please, don't throw us off!
It's been a long time...
But we're finally back.
Ahh! Any dragons?
Mika-san?
Bridge! Right below us!
It's approaching!
Capella! Going full starboard!
Right away!
-Berko...
-Vadakin...
What the heck is that?
It's a pod...
It's a huge pod of little dragons!
Okay, we finally found it!
That's... they gathered and formed
a bubble?
It's like a huge dragon dango!
That is a "ferry".
So that's what we were looking for.
That means we nailed it!
It was about time that fortune
started smiling on us!
We won't be able to use anchors
and bomb lances on this one...
Eh? Why?
What's with you? Think a little
about our prey's size.
Eh?
From what we can see, a single
dragon is about twice as tall as Gibbs.
If we shot an anchor or
bomb lances at one of those
what do you think would happen?
Ah! They would be torn to pieces!
Right?
Don't use me in your explanations!
You know, those little ones are great
because you can eat the meat on the bone.
Sinking your teeth directly
into the meat...
Their tails would go great in a soup too...
It's been a long time since
we used that.
Amazing...
There we go! It's pulling!
If we tighten the rope so much,
we'll end up losing the prey!
Let the rope run till it weakens!
Argh, it burns!
I can't hold it with this friction...
Takita! Pour water on the rope!
Yes!
Only 20 meters of rope left!
Right! Pull!
Mika, pull it toward us.
We'll shot a second harpoon at it.
Takita!
-Use the spear at your feet!
-Yes!
Takita...!
Hey... you're kidding...
She... she fell...?
Move!
Bridge! Takita has fallen!
Drop our course inmediately!
That girl...
She was clinging on to the dragon,
wasn't she?
She is gonna be okay, I think.
Am I alive?
Ah... almost forgot...
The ointment Nanami-san
gave me.
I wonder what is this place...
I need to do my best for the ship
to find me.
But... what should I do?
Ah... that's it.
So hot!
Ah... I really did it!
I'm so glad I learned how
to start a fire properly.
I've gotta thank Jiro-san.
With just this, there's not
going to be enough smoke.
I need to build up the flame more.
It's no use.
Ah... it's suffering.
Return peacefully to the clouds
and grant us good winds.
I'm sorry I couldn't
hunt you well...
Forgive me.
Where did you come from?
Could it be...?
-Hey, Takita!!
-Takitaaa!!
-Takita!!
You... you can't be for real...
Answer us, damn it!!
Takita has fallen...
Tsk...
We can't land the ship in this
treacherous place.
Takita... shit...
She was such a good girl...
Don't say such ominous things!
We don't know anything yet for sure!
Ah! Jiro!
It'll be faster if I look
for her in this.
Mika!
I'll be watching behind you,
let's go.
Damn it!
Don't look at me with those eyes.
I need to take its entrails out
and cool down its meat.
If I don't, all of it will go to waste.
Please, go away, anywhere but here.
I can't dissect it well enough
with this.
I... can't do anything about this...
I'm a draker after all.
Are you worried about me?
And now, of all times...
is when my body starts to tremble?
Let me rest for a moment.
I dozed off.
Oh? Where's the little one?
Heey!
Where are you?!
Hey!
Geez... Don't wander off on your own!
I knew that the presence I sensed
wasn't a wild goat.
That floaty little thing,
is that a dragon?
Ah! Wh- who are you?!
That's my line!
You entered someone else's territory
without even saying hello!
Mmm?
Eh??
It's the first time I see
a dragon alive so close!
Is this a cub?
- I'm Ascella, a matagi hunter.
-Eh?
These are my hunting grounds.
Ah... so you were a woman!
You should be able to tell
from my voice.
Ah, um...
I fell from a draking vessel
with an injured dragon...
Wait a second.
You fell from the sky
and survived?!
Wow! What a disaster you went through!
Ah... so that means you're
one of those drakers.
Ah... do you have a knife?!
Eh? Of course, I'm a matagi hunter.
I tasted dragon meat once before,
but dissecting it is a first for me!
Ah... this one is rather a small one.
We call everything a dragon, but
their types and sizes are very different...
How come it can fly without wings?
The dragons...
Fly with this.
"Dragon heart"
Even if they have different shapes...
All dragons have a heart like this one.
Ehh? Just with this?
It doesn't look very tasty...
Now that you mention it, the heart is so
hard that it's not edible.
Eh? Hey, are you okay?
Eh! Wai-!
You're burning up!
Mika, we don't have much fuel left.
We'll have to go back to the ship soon.
Yeah.
Jiro!
It's no good, the valley is so
much more complicated than I thought...
Once we refuel, we're setting out again!
-No way!
-Eh?
I won't allow that! The sun's setting soon.
You'll set out in this first
thing tomorrow morning.
Gibbs! You know that I can see well
in the dark! Let me try once more!
Do you think I can allow that
and lose you too?
Ah... the sun is setting.
If we continue like this and lose
our field of vision, the ship will be in trouble too.
What should we do...?
Deputy captain, raise our course
above the cliffs
and then...
Following the protocol, we'll declare the next
48 hours as the search period.
Is that good?
Mmm?
Yeah...
This place has a very complicated terrain.
Don't lower our course too much.
Continue the sailing in zigzag
at a low speed.
Crocco-san,
fires are not allowed at the bridge...
Nevermind...
♪〜
Translation: TomoyaNC   Proofreading: akemilena