Well, this will be worth dissecting!
Mika-san,
are all those people
dissection masters too?
Yeah, they undertake the dissection
of huge dragons.
I see... their tools have a very
particular shape too.
Aw, man... where did
our vacation go...
Ugh... booze...
This is not what we were told...
Yesterday was fun, though...
I'm so sleepy...
Come on, guys, don't be lazy!
Hey, if there are dissection
masters and all...
Why do we have to do it too?
That's what you get for the mess
you caused at the bar.
Stop complaining and do it!
C'mon, go to the altar!
Riiiiight...
Can we pray too?
Yes.
-Let's go.
-Yes!
Rest... and return...
To the skies, to the skies...
Be one with the earth,
one with the life...
With the life...
Return thee... return thee...
Fortunately, no one was hurt
in this incident...
But the city was badly damaged.
We wanted to be of help
even if it was only a little bit...
So we drakers ended up helping
with the dissection all together.
I'm more than glad to help the city,
but...
we can't even think about the festival now.
♪〜
〜♪
Okay, great, over here, don't stop...
Hey! Don't push it!
Thanks for the help, we didn't
have enough people.
No problem, I was just thinking
what should I do for the crew's lunch.
You really don't mind
giving me so many ingredients?
Yeah, since the festival was cancelled
we weren't going to use them anyway.
If they're gonna go bad,
I'd rather use them for emergency food.
The townsfolk are working hard
on reconstructing the city, too.
I see!
So, we're making soup?
Nope, it's something that was made
so that peasants could have lunch outside.
Local cuisine that can be cooked
in a cauldron.
Ohh, then that's perfect
for emergency food indeed.
Not as much as you'd think!
Huh?
Melt the dragon fat in the cauldron,
put in some caraway and onion and
stir-fry it until it gets a golden colour.
Yeah, yeah...
Hey, you! You better not put
potatoes in there!
-Ah... there we go.
-Of course I will!
Tsk! We don't put that thing in it!
Hey...
This has no bacon!
What?
That's goulash, isn't it?
If you don't fry the bacon
with the onion,
it will taste bad!
Katja, go get some from the
bar's kitchen, will you?
Sure.
Leave this one to me.
Ah... okay, okay.
See? I told you.
This kind of dish is cooked
differently in every family.
Everyone thinks theirs is the best
and that's why they always argue.
I see.
By the way, what about the meat?
From what I see, it's all dragon meat,
but of many types and parts.
You can put whatever meat
you want, right?
Yeah.
Actually, putting a lot of different
kinds of meat is the Quon city style.
Yep, yep.
I see.
This is a city where
many different dragons gather,
so it's a taste you only can find here.
And on top of this, some meat
cut in big sized pieces,
sprinkle some salt, and...
Enough powdered paprika
to cover all the meat.
Eh, you're putting that much?
It's bright red!
And then, garlic and
celery tied with a thread.
Diced tomatoes, paprika and water...
And we let it simmer for 2 whole hours.
Ohh, I'm looking forward to this!
Where did you learn that?
I've done it once before.
Wow, those two are good at this.
Gibbs-san, sorry for the wait!
Okay, get up here!
Eh? What is it?
We're gonna scoop out some brain oil.
Brain oil?
It's a very high-grade oil accumulated
in the head. We were very lucky,
because not all dragons have this.
We're going to get inside it
and pump it out.
Wait... what?!
Inside... its head?
Ugh... for real?
What can we do? We're the smallest
around here.
Ugh...
Eh?
Takita, hurry it up!
Come on!
It's so sticky...
Ow...
Ew, it smells fishy...
This is also a draker's job...
And then, when the potatoes
and carrots are cooked...
It's done.
Good.
-Um...
-Yeah?
You're in Jiro's ship, right?
Eh? Yeah...
How is he like?
Jiro, huh...
Let's see...
Ahhh, I'm so hungry!
-Lunch time!
-It smells so good!
Working for free sure makes you
hungrier than usual.
Good job out there.
Oh, Katja!
You cooked too?
-Only a bit.
-I see!
Well, while we wait for this to
finish cooking...
Let's make another thing over there!
This is the red meat of the dragon
we brought to this city.
Ah, the one I dissected!
We'll simply just hit it!
Hit it?
We'll hit it as if we were pulling it
and stretch it thin.
Ah, I want to do it!
How about this?
Yeah, well done.
Then, some salt and pepper,
sprinkle some flour,
coat it evenly with egg
and cover it with cheese
mixed with breadcrumbs.
Melt some dragon fat and butter
in a big frypan, and...
One, two...!
Could this be...
-Yoshi-san, this is...!
-Yeah.
You've been wanting to eat it
for a long time, right?
Good, that's a nice colour.
Hop!
A dragon cutlet, extra large!
Oh boy, what's this smell?
This is...
Man, this can't go wrong in any way!
Yoshi-san, you're the best!
Then, let's eat it togeth...
Ahh!!
Wait, Mika-san! That's for everyone!
Damn you...!
Hey! Someone get Mika away
from the cutlet!
He's gonna eat it all!
Don't monopolize it!
Say, the people from your ship
are always like this?
Ah... yeah.
It looks so fun, how nice!
Yep!
"Dragon cutlet and Quon-style goulash"
So good!
Ah, Faye! Your cutlet
is bigger than mine!
Aw come on, you're so fussy.
Gibbs, do we have any more
work after this?
We're supposed to continue
until sunset...
Ah... I see.
Ah... I see...
Yoshi-san, seconds!
How many seconds have you eaten?
-Okay, line up!
-That's unfair for the others!
Just a little bit!
-Here, for you, Jiro.
-Thank you.
This is the specialty of our city.
And we add bacon to the goulash, you know?
Wow!
Oh! So good!
This somehow looks...
Like a festival, don't you think?
It's true!
Mika-san, you're eating too much!
Might as well just drink some alcohol!
Ah?!
I'm joking...
I think a glass won't hurt.
Damn right!
Stop yelling!
So... about the method
to extract the poison.
Add a lot of salt and water
that has been boiled once to rice bran,
and just pickle the meat in that.
Rice bran?
And that will extract the poison?
The wisdom of our ancestors is
not to be taken lightly.
Ohh...
Put the meat and the rice bran
alternatively in a pottery jar,
close it with a lid, and seal it with a cloth.
Bury it for about three years in the earth,
and wait for the poison to disappear.
I see...!
What did you just say?
I never said that you could
eat it right away...
Ah! Wait, Mika-san!
What are you doing
to the poor old man!
Three years...
Mika, help us fill the jars.
Well, time for us to go back
to our own job.
Katja! Let's go.
At this rate, I think we'll
finish dissecting it today.
Then I guess we can leave
tomorrow morning.
Yes, please do that.
What?!
We were able to refuel and repair
the ship, but our gains are essentially none.
We can't even think of a vacation...
I... guess that's true, but...
My massage...
What?
It's... it's nothing.
I do understand how you feel, though.
But we shouldn't stay long here.
For the sake of the people
of this city as well, we should leave soon.
Right...
It's true...
Ah, Mika-san! You're skipping work again!
Wha? We finished dissecting it,
so what does it matter?
Geez...
We're leaving in the morning, huh?
Hm? Yeah.
Too bad we couldn't see the festival.
Ahhh!
I really wanted to eat that dragon.
Hey, what do you think it tastes like?
Eh...
I don't know about that yet...
Ahh, good grief! It's finally over!
It took three whole days...
That dragon was way too huge!
That's all we can do.
Now it's up to the townspeople.
Good job today!
Oh, Takita, you too, you worked hard.
Okay, it's time! Time to drink!
Yeah, nice voice there!
We need to prepare for the departure.
Whaaat?
For real...?
Takita, where's Jiro?
Wasn't he with you?
He said he was going back first.
Well, isn't it fine?
Jiro...!
Sorry for the wait.
Come with me!
Where are we going?
Wow, what is this?
It's called autogyro.
The guys from the other ship
gave it to us in gratitude.
Here, put this on!
I practiced a lot until
I was able to ride it well!
Katja, hop on!
Eh? What?
Hold onto me tight!
Sure!
Up we go!
Wow!!
I'm flying!
You said you had never
left the city, right?
Eh?
Look.
We're outside the city.
When the sun finishes rising...
We'll... leave the town.
I see...
Katja...
Will you...
come with me...
to the ship...
Don't...
If you talk that much...
you'll bite your tongue...
Ohh, it's wonderful!
Thank you so much for bringing it!
I'll add this to the tapestry too.
Also, Takita, put out your arm.
Hm?
Oh...!
It's an amulet I made with a scrap.
Also, an ointment made with the mucus
of a small kind of dragon called salamandra.
It's good for erasing scars.
Nanami-san... Thank you so much!
Make sure you come back.
Yesh!
We're gonna leave, get boarding!
Riiiight.
Be well.
For the time you come back,
the meat will most likely be edible.
You better leave some for me!
Back to living in the sky again, huh?
The sky's our lover, I guess.
-Sadly...
-What the hell?
I should get going too.
Well then, Katja...
Jiro...
Katja...
I'm gonna cut your hair!
Eh?
With this, you kind of
look like a girl.
It won't take me more than five minutes!
Can you lend me scissors and a sheet?
S-sure, I think we have some in the ship.
Vannie!
Can you lend me a pair of scissors?
I'll return them right away!
Sure... take your time.
I'm so glad I met you.
Take care.
Three years, really?
Come on... are you still going on
about that, Mika-san?
Freshen up!
Mika!
Let's go to the lookout.
Yeah.
-Hm?
-Eh?!
Jiro-san?
Eh?! What happened?!
Why does it matter?
I'll be at the front and
you at the back, Mika.
U-um, Jiro-san!
Takita.
Boys have a lot going on for them, too.
I'll be at the front.
No, me.
Oh no, it'll be me.
No way in hell, me!
-Me at the front!
-Me!!
-Me.
-Me, me!
No, me.
-No, I'll be the one!
-Me.
Why?! I'm also an adult now!
Please, be my guest.
♪〜
Translation: akemilena   Proofreading: TomoyaNC