Even though they're called draking vessels,
it's not like we're fighting dragons
every day.
Actually, it's the everyday work
which is the hardest.
Ah... Jiro-san.
Hm? Takita.
-Time to switch?
-Yeah.
You're on laundry duty?
Yes! I'm good at doing laundry.
Really...?
Leave it to me!
Up we go...
Is she gonna be alright...?
How rare for you to have
a hangover, Vanabelle.
Here, honey and ginger juice.
I just had a drink before sleep...
It was a mixed drink...
Cheap alcohol's not good.
Spicy...
Yoshi-san, do you have any laundry?
Oh, then take that towel, please.
Oh? Vannie-san.
Are you okay?
I'll help you when I finish this.
It's fine! Please rest.
Any laundry?
Takita, shut up for a bit.
Eh?
This is a fight between men.
If you want to give up, you better
do it before it's too late.
Ha! As if!
Now...
It's on!
Ahh!! Why!!
A fight between men...
You should just stop!
Soraya, you're terrible with bets.
Shut your mouth, Faye!
You better pay me
when you get your next wage.
I know...
Well, now...
Oh, Takita, good timing.
Pour some water on me.
Is that shampoo? Sure!
It's nice how it's been
pretty calm lately, right?
What are you saying?
Now's when it gets busy,
so get ready.
Is it gonna be that hectic?
Yeah, it will be like shooting fish
in a barrel.
We can't possibly miss it.
I see...
Um? When was the last time
I washed my hair?
Ah? Want me to lend you some washing powder?
Ah, no...
I have a lot of hair
and it's troublesome to wash so I kinda...
Takita...
Yes...?
Sometimes... you never know
what you've got till it's gone...
You're actually concerned about it...
Wh-what is it, Mika-san?
Do... do I stink?
It's a lot of trouble, but...
it's a fun... workplace... yes.
♪〜
〜♪
29%.
29 per cent...
Wow, I can't believe you can guess
the position of the ship so high in the sky.
It's amazing!
It's impossible for me,
I don't understand a thing!
Jiro-san, you're so skillful!
Anyone on a ship should be able
to do this much.
If you follow the process in order,
anyone can do it.
Everyone's just too sloppy.
Gibbs-san said it though!
That your observations are
the most accurate!
Who teached you?
My dad.
Eh?
My dad... was a draker too.
Ahh! Now I understand!
Your dad must have been outstanding!
He was really irresponsible.
Casually coming home, and then
going out again just as casually.
Leaving me and my mom alone.
When he came home,
he only talked about dragons.
There has been not a single sign of them
for the past week.
With this weather, we can't expect much either.
Either way, if we continue like this,
we'll be deep in the red.
Oh dear...
It shouldn't have been like this...
What do we do, Crocco?
Uh... we also need to refuel already...
Let's go across the sea towards northwest
and find some land.
Excuse me!
-Gibbs-san, here.
-Thanks.
Crocco-san, I think a storm is
approaching after all.
Ah?
It's true...
The pressure on the mercury column is dropping.
Gibbs.
Grab the guys that are off-duty today
and go check if the cargo is properly secured.
Got it.
Okay, let's go.
Yes!
I'll join you later.
Sure.
Jiro-san, how did you know
a storm is coming?
Because the wind feels a bit lukewarm.
I see...
Sometimes you can know
because of the smell, too.
Ah... now that you mention it,
I smell something... burning...
Eh?
Eh?! A fire?!
What are you doing?!
Smoking meat.
The fire was too strong and it
made too much smoke.
You see, we had some old salted meat.
Here's the red meat, and below that, fat meat.
We're using grappa from an oak barrel
so it'll smell really nice!
Yep, with every little adjustment
the flavor can change in unexpected ways.
Smoking is pretty deep.
I can't stop looking at it...?!
Wait... stop!
Come on! You're going too, Mika-san.
A storm is coming!
No, I gotta watch over the smoked meat!
Not like you can do anything here.
-S... stop I tell you!
-Come on!
I bet you just wanted to snitch food.
Come on, let's go. You help too, Mika.
Fine...
Don't pile it up.
Put it down and fix it.
Yes!
The clouds are starting to look pretty bad.
Jiro!
Maybe today is the day we finally see it!
See what?
Why does it matter?
It's fine, tell her about it.
The story of the glittering dragon.
Gibbs!
Glittering dragon?
What's the glittering dragon?
Once upon a time, a ship ran across a storm.
Dad, what happened to that ship?
Ah, the storm just got stronger
and stronger,
and everyone aboard came to terms
with the fact that they were done for.
Obstructed by thunderclouds,
and with their compass broken,
they couldn't tell south from north.
But in that moment,
between the clouds, they could see a light.
Lightning?
No, not that.
Eh?
Someone said
"This light comes from a town!
We'll be saved!"
But something was weird.
That light was slowly approaching
the ship.
And what appeared before the crew members
holding their breath was...
A glittering dragon.
It was as if the ship was bewitched,
and it was drawn in to that dragon.
Who knows how much time passed...
but when they noticed, they had left
the storm behind.
The glittering dragon saved them!
It's just a legend.
Among the drakers,
there are a few of those superstitions
going around.
You know, before Jiro came to this ship,
he believed his dad's stories.
Right?
That happened a long time ago!
Why are you always bringing up things
from when I was a newbie...
When you're on a ship, there's nothing
but troubles!
I sure wish a dragon saved us!
Yeah, definitely.
If a dragon like that exists,
I'd love to see it.
No, it maybe does exist.
What?
After all, no one has ever seen
all the dragons.
If I ate a glittering dragon...
do you think my stomach would shine?
From the inside, like bam!
Hell if I know...
Guys, I don't see you working!
I'm going to keep watch.
The wind has gotten quite strong.
Should we change the course?
No, it's too late.
The clouds are growing too fast.
The storm already caught us.
Uh... everyone listen!
The weather has gotten rough!
The storm is coming!
Niko and Oken who are on duty,
to the bridge,
Faye and Soraya go help the engine room,
everyone else stand by on your cabins.
Anything else, follow Gibbs' orders.
Old man!
You two check over there.
If it stops now, it'll fall apart!
Yes ma'am!
We're always so reckless...
I wish we had a more... safe sail...
I know right.
-Move your hands!
-Yes ma'am!
Good grief...
Everyone, put your safety belts on!
-Also, Capella!
-Yes!
Go to the toilet while you can.
Jiro, you don't need to
keep watch anymore!
Get down here before you get blown away.
I can see the clouds better here
than in the bridge!
If I don't predict the flow of the clouds,
we won't be able to get out of the storm.
I'll stay and keep at it!
But you know...
Mika!
Jiro, you have great eyes,
we're counting on you.
Switch with me. I'll be on the front,
you behind.
Mika...
Here.
Smoked salty salo, freshly made.
We're not in a picnic, you know?
You can't keep watch with
an empty stomach.
It's coming.
Don't let the clouds at the front distract you!
Look at the flow!
We know!
A wall of clouds at 2 o'clock.
It goes all the way to the back.
Jiro, do you think we can
pass through that side?
Hey!
Y-yeah...
It's probably fine.
Good.
Go over the clouds at 9 o'clock.
30 to port!
Go above the clouds.
Raise the tail!
Yes!
This goddamn storm...
The rudder feels so heavy!
Engine room! We're increasing the output!
-Ahh, come on!
-Check over there!
Yes!
Not both of you!
Right...!
Good...
The clouds on the front were hiding it...
No way...
Make the ship stand in the wind!
We can't! We're being swept away!
If we continue like this we won't
be able to escape!
Jiro, don't let it shake you off!
We've been surrounded...
We can't lift it anymore!
Can't we cut through the clouds?!
It's a vortex of air currents!
We'd be torn to pieces!
The only option is to slip between the clouds.
-Right...
-For real?
That was close...
So close...
Takita, come here.
You should get away from the window.
Y-yes!
Vannie-san...
Oh?
What are you doing?
Do I stink?
Eh?
What are you saying at a time like this?
I wonder if Mika-san and Jiro-san are okay...
I just hope Jiro doesn't do anything reckless...
Jiro, how's it?
So far so good, keep going straight.
Don't change the course!
It's electrified?
This is...!
A chance we'll probably never have again,
being able to fly in the middle of this storm.
Eh?
The thunderclouds will bring us the dragon.
If it's going to appear,
it has to be under this sky.
Mika, let me sit at the front.
Being at the front all the time
wears you out.
What? I'm fine.
We don't know when will we able to
get out of this storm.
That light was slowly approaching
the ship.
And what appeared before the crew members
holding their breath was...
That was...
A glittering dragon.
Wow...
Guys, look towards port!
What, what?
This is...
Unbelievable...
Crocco!
Yeah, I'm seeing it.
Let's...
-Capture it!
-The hell?!
Are you insane?!
We're in the middle of a storm!
How do you plan to capture it?!
We better do it quick or it'll get away!
What are you talking about?!
-Just listen to me and
bring the ship closer!
-As if I could!
Mika, move!
Crocco-san!
That dragon will show us the way.
If we follow it, we should be able
to get out of the storm!
Hey, hey, are you for real?
If the dragon is flying
avoiding the thunderclouds
it could be possible!
Sounds fun, I think we should trust him.
Deputy captain!
If we capture that dragon, we'd be rolling in it!
Agh! If it's not one it's the other!
Jiro, I leave this to you.
Wh- hey!
Mika!
Mika... were you really planning on
catching it?
We were lucky we got to slip out
of the storm at all.
I can't believe I let such a big prey
escape from under my own nose...
It's fine, let the legend be a legend.
Legends won't fill your stomach, you know?
Guys, the food is ready!
Oh! What do we have today?
Go on ahead.
Takita...
There's no meat in here...?
Eh?
There is though,
look.
You can't call this meat!
What do you want me to do?
That's what happens when we don't
catch dragons!
There's not much food left!
If you're gonna complain
I'm taking it away!
Thanks for the food...
Delicious.
♪〜
Translation: akemilena   Proofreading: TomoyaNC