Ah... that Takita...
I can't believe she fell off the ship...
Yeah... if we had been more careful...
It's no one's fault.
But even if you say that...
Ah... to think this is the
last image we'd have of her...
And here I was throwing my pants
and whatnot at her every day...
Forgive me, Takita!
All things considered,
she was a good girl...
Yeah...
In three or so years she'd have
shined as a draker...
Ahh!! Come on, you guys!
Stop being so ominous, would you?!
But, you know...
Guys... even if they're wounded,
dragons not always fall head first.
So if she was clinging on to it
until the end...
Maybe... she's safe.
You can say whatever you want, but...
We barely can't even see anymore...
How are we even going to search for her...
Ah, Yoshi-san, make me
some salo sandwiches.
Also, very sweet tea.
-Eh?
-What?
I'll be on guard without sleeping tonight.
I just can't imagine it.
Her being turned to mincemeat, I mean.
So she's alive.
Probably...
We... didn't manage to catch
that dragon, damn it.
♪〜
〜♪
You gotta thank this little guy.
It's been protecting you all this time.
It might think you're its mother
or something.
I guess that injury on your leg
got infected.
If I didn't happen to pass by
this deep chasm,
you'd have died in the gutter.
Ah, what happened to the dissection?
I took out the entrails and have it
submerged over there.
You sure have luck on your side, though.
Luck's always been about the only
thing I had going for me.
Um, what is this...?
I always make it with deer or boar,
"Salted cabbage and dragon brain hunter stew
with roasted bone marrow"
but with dragon it's the first time...
I hope you don't mind I used
some of your dragon's head.
It's a stew made by matagi hunters.
Mm, what a nice smell!
This is my favourite dish!
Let's see...
How does a dragon's brain taste?
I don't think I'm hungry...
But you have to eat!
You're pretty weakened, you know?
If you don't eat while you have some
strength left, you won't be able to
stomach anything later on.
It's because it's this little one's mother?
So good!
It's sticky but smooth.
What an intense flavour!
Ahhh! I can feel the nourishment
permeating in every single of my organs!
Are you doing it on purpose?
Yes I am.
So mean...
I'm just honest.
Why are you crying?
Because... it's so good...
Yeah...
It's super delicious.
We gotta thank its mother, right?
Mom!!
You have to eat the preys you hunt.
You know, the more you eat
the better you live!
There's someone similar to you
in my ship.
He's a man, though.
Hm? Really?
Do you want seconds?
Yes, please!
Wow, a camp in a place like this...
We, the matagi,
hunt with this area as a base
during this season.
Hm? My, how rare.
Do we have a guest?
Hey!
Oh, and a little one as well.
I bet everyone is worried...
Or they think I'm already dead
and left already...
What?
The ointment?
Yep.
I'm definitely gonna bring you
back to your pod.
In that case
You need to be in perfect health first.
Hmm... it's quite swollen...
I did all I could, but...
Eh? Huh? Ascella-san?
Wh-what is this?
Takita, bite this leaf and endure it
for a bit, okay?
Don't worry!
Granny is an expert with the needle.
Takita, look at this landscape.
It's... kind of amazing.
It lets out some smoke every few years.
Mount Kin...
It's said that when that mountain
lets out smoke, dragons will pass by.
Dragons...
Does the smoke call the dragons?
Who knows, it's just a superstition
after all.
It's not.
Fishes swim in the sea,
beasts walk on the mountains,
dragons fly in the sky,
and people live on the land.
According to the legend,
our ancestors
arrived to this valley chasing dragons.
I see...
Chased out of their lands,
our ancestors, who were travelling
searching for a new world,
saw a dragon fall from the sky
and followed its trail.
And they arrived to this valley.
They thought it was some kind of good omen,
and decided to live here.
Yep, and that's done.
-Rest for a while, okay?
-Yes, yes.
Ah... thank you very much.
It looks kinda down, doesn't it?
It's hungry too...
I think...
Wheat porridge.
Yoghurt.
Bean paste.
Nothing works.
It seems it doesn't like any of these.
Hmmm...
Ah, I know.
It's a creature from the sky,
so maybe it eats things from the sky?
Hm? Things from the sky?
Ah!
Some time ago, a small dragon
happened to get into the ship.
It was drawn in by the smell
of dragon oil...
Insert the blade between the red meat
and the fat and cut it away along with the skin.
When you've cut it in pieces,
Leave a bit of skin and add
some thin cuts.
It looks... kind of like a book.
Actually, this is called
"making into a book".
While it boils, scoop out
the oil that floats
and after it's extracted,
add the oil cake as fuel...
Ah, some people eat it too.
And that's dragon oil done!
You got quite a lot.
You can use it both for cooking
and as lamp oil.
Ohh, nice.
Come here.
Look, it's dragon oil.
Eat it.
Please, do it... okay?
You have to eat!
Why...?
I can't bear looking at this.
Granny?
How about we add an egg?
Eh, an egg?
When she was feeling down,
I used to make it for her like this too.
I see.
Wha- that was a long time ago.
Takita, pour the oil slowly.
Little by little, like a thread.
Okay.
Ah, I'll do it.
All that's left is to continue mixing it
while you add the oil, she says.
Ah, it's thickening!
"Mayonnaise with dragon oil and whole egg"
Good, good.
Here...
It ate it...!
It's eating, it's eating!
Thank you so much!
Hold the little thing and give it to it.
She looks like a real mom!
I wonder what are Mika-san
and the others doing right now...
What... are they eating...
Why... what?
Mm... what's wrong?
The little one!
Ah... it's all wrinkly!
It ate properly and all...
Fish in the sea...
beasts in the mountain...
Dragons in the sky...
This one... probably can't live on land.
The wind...
The mountain is letting out
a lot of smoke...
When the smoke blows,
dragons will pass by...
Takita?
Ascella-san, I'm going!
Wait... you're going
to the mountain now?
No, you can't with that leg!
It's absurd!
At least wait till the sun goes up...
If I wait, it'll be too late.
It has never seen other dragons like
itself nor flown in the sky.
If I abandon it here...
I... have the feeling I won't be able
to go back to being a draker.
No, I'm the one who saved you.
If you're gonna let that go to waste
I won't forgive you!
I'm gonna prepare, so wait a bit!
Thank you so much for everything.
Ugh! It hurts...
See, what did I tell you?
Want me to go slower?
No, I'll manage!
That mountain is very steep.
Even matagi hunters don't go
there often... damn it.
Boy, if I ain't kind to a fault!
Takita, want to rest for a while?
I-I'm fine... this pain isn't even
the worst I've had...
A shadow?
You sure you didn't mistake it?
Yes.
It quickly hid behind the clouds,
but it was definitely that dragon pod.
Or it should be...
"Should", huh?
Takita, it gets way too dangerous
after this.
Haven't you done enough?
I haven't!
I need to go...
As far as I can...
As high as I can...
As closer as possible!
But, girl...
I wonder what makes you go that far.
I'm the same as you, Ascella-san.
Huh?
I'm just honest.
Don't lump me with you!
You're so honest you need to add
"stupidly" before it.
Ehh?!
This is the point where Takita fell.
During the search, we detected
the dragon pod again.
We started pursuing it and
lost sight of it here.
Like Gaga said,
that pod is on their way to
a certain place.
That "ferry" definitely has a destination.
I agree with that, but
thinking that this final destination
is where Takita-san will be
isn't a bit too optimistic?
No, there's the possibility
that the dragon that fell with her
continued flying chasing the pod.
We don't have any other clue anyway.
Yeah.
If we know their destination,
we can also follow the way back.
We can narrow down the search scope
quite a lot.
Ah... we have half a day left.
Let's go with this, it's our only bet.
I'll take your place.
You have barely slept, right?
And you're the same.
The horizon is lighting up...
Go back to your room and sleep.
When I was in front of her...
I was surprisingly talkative.
I wonder why.
How would I know?
Find her, and discover it yourself.
Yeah.
Hmm... even if we call it destination,
who knows where on earth are
the dragons heading to.
And with this field of vision,
if we don't narrow down
the area even more, we can't...
Is there anything bothering you?
No, it's just...
Excuse me...
Do you have a moment?
It seems there's a legend about dragons
in the stories of the matagi of this area...
Look, this is probably...
talking about the "ferry",
or so I thought...
Is that trustworthy?
No, but...
I see.
Maybe we should believe in it.
We'll find Takita, won't we?
I'll go first.
Takita, don't look down!
For the love of...!
Taki...!
You...
That's bad for my heart...
Thank you.
Ah, the wind...
The pod... is changing its shape...
Is it going somewhere?!
You see it, right?
Those are your friends.
I'll give this to you.
I'm sure it'll protect you.
Ride the wind and go back to the sky!
You need to go!
Quick!
If you don't hurry up,
they'll leave you behind, go!!
Don't come back, I tell you!
You're...
a dragon!!
Quin... Zaza...
♪〜
Translation: akemilena   Proofreading: TomoyaNC