Good thing this didn't burn.
Right!
That's our prey, to begin with.
As if I could let them take
300 barrel of dragon oil from
under our noses!
We'll finish it off.
Did it work?
No way!
That's dangerous!
Those jerks just added
more fuel to the fire!
Engine room! How long until takeoff?!
We can't do more than this!
This is bad!
How the fuck isn't it dead
after all those bombs?
It should be dead with all the poison,
I can't believe it!
Ah...! There is the...!
We shook it off...
Yeah...
Well... thanks for doing something stupid!
The plan begins now!
Be on time for once in your lives!
Goddamnit...
Now's our time to move!
Yeah!
I'm sure this was
because we let our guard down.
Even though we barely knew anything
about how dragons lived.
This tragedy...
Was something we drakers
brought upon ourselves.
♪〜
〜♪
Ah... what a terrible sight...
Bridge!
I can't aim with so many obstacles!
Raise our course and find me a place
with a clear line of fire!
Ah? What happened to the plan?
We're in the middle of the city!
Is there a place like that?
This looks awful...
You can't tell there was
a town here...
At least it seems that
all the people here evacuated safely...
Ah! Jiro-san!
What were you doing here?
Mika...
It can't fly anymore.
Let's put it out of its misery.
Oh?
Is that building over there
an oil refinery?
You're kidding!
It if catches fire all this area
will be a sea of flames!
-Ah...
-Mika-san!
Can't help it! We'll finish it
off right here!
Vadakin! You and the rest go
surround it!
Understood! You guys, come with me!
-Yeah!
-Yes, sir!
-Let's all cover Mika!
-Roger!
Fire!
It doesn't seem to do anything!
What the hell is the
air team doing?
Isn't it because the dragon is
in a place where the Quin Zaza can't aim?
Yeah, that's what it seems.
We didn't think we would be
fighting in the middle of the streets!
Shit! That Gibbs,
what shitty plan is this?
We're almost out of bomb lances!
This big bastard...
In that case how about switching to
stun lances, Takita?
Right away!
Vannie-san!
Please, work...
There's no effect!
The bullets we are firing
can't cause it to bleed enough!
They aren't even breaking
through its skin!
What a waste... these aren't cheap!
Hey!
It's too dangerous, run!
If guns don't work...
Guess I'll go with this.
Mika-san!
Is he planning to stab that monster
with only a spear?
Mika is going there, don't fire!
We can't run anymore.
Niko! Cover me!
Oh, hey! Don't give me that you too!
Tsk...
Isn't he starting to act like Mika?
-Mika!
-Mika-san!
I told ya!
Mika-san!
Are you okay?
You're bleeding a lot...
Takita...
Bring me... bring me a spear.
What are you saying?
You can't go with that wound!
You'll die!
There's already
one of our spears stabbed in its body.
Now's our prey.
We must hunt it properly...
And eat it whole!
Hunt, dissect and eat...
That's all drakers are about.
See? You can't go like that...
It's impossible!
Ah! This looks bad!
It's going to burn all of us
with its heat ray!
-What the hell's that?
-Looks dangerous!
-Wait, wait, wait!
-This again?!
Everyone, retreat!
Hurry up! Evade its line of fire!
Where is it aiming though?
Shut up and run!
Ah... we failed...
Wait... Jiro-san?
Hey... what the hell is he doing?!
Look! Right there!
It's Jiro!
He's climbing onto the dragon!
Eh? Jiro-san?
There's... no time to lose!
Hey! What the hell are you doing?!
Run away, you idiot!
Wait! Jiro...!
How can I run after all of this?!
If I shoot the weak point
in its spine...
If it's at point-blank...!
Not yet... I can't give up yet!
Jirooo!!
Are you for real?
It's the Quin Zaza!
Way to go.
Hey! Do this more carefully!
Do you plan to wreck the ship
or what?
Crocco-san, didn't you tell me
to ram it without fear?!
I did say to ram it but...
I didn't say it was okay to
break the ship in half!
I can't do one without the other!
Ah!
It's going to fall apart!
Quick! Reverse the engine!
Cha-changing gears!
Wah! We're falling down!
Increasing power!
Be careful!
Niko!
Are you... hurt?
-We did it!
-Finally!
They pulled quite a stunt...
I can't imagine what Lee-san
is gonna say about this...
Ah...!
Jiro! Well done!
You attracted its attention
flawlessly!
Let's go!
Yeaaah!
-It is really over?
-Did they kill it?
Hey! The city's all ruins now!
Ah! My precious bar!
Shit... why did this happen to me...
In the end... we needed
each and every spear to finish it off...
We're pretty sloppy drakers, huh?
Ah... all this bleeding...
Doesn't it hurt?
It hurts like hell
'cause I'm still alive.
Ahh... our poor little ship.
What are you taking the ship for?
The airscrews are fine!
You can fly away!
Ah... I'm so glad...
Well, I'm not glad!
We're doing damage control as
soon as we dock!
Mmm?
Jiro!
Eh...? Katja!
I'm so glad you're safe!
Yeah!
I was so worried when I saw
the bar destroyed!
Everyone evacuated and we're
safe and sound.
Thank god...
Don't exagerate.
I was really worried.
Oh? Really worried about me?
Ah...!
A-... about everyone!
That brat! As soon as I take
my eyes off him...
Getting a head start, eh?
Not bad for him, the scoundrel!
Waah! What a pretty girl!
Phew!
So... without further ado!
A little kiss of reunion.
Eh... wai- Huh?!
You can't treat a customer like that!
It won't move anymore?
Yeah.
You guys put it down finally.
Yeah... you can say that.
Now that I look at it closely
it's pretty frightening.
Are you gonna dissect it right away?
Yeah...
But, since it has poison in its
system and we fired stun lances at it...
Even if we dissect it...
It is not good enough to sell it?
It's not like that.
But its value has gone down
quite considerably.
Though that's only a problem
we have to face ourselves.
Value... huh?
Ah, what's that?
A fight? I wonder...
Well? What are you going to do?
Because of your "little" mistake
the city has suffered a tragedy!
You are able to fly in the sky
because this city buys all it can
from you, drakers!
And you thank us like this?!
If we didn't bring dragons here,
the ones who couldn't live
would be you!
We are always risking our lives
up there!
Uh! Now you've said it!
Who do you think you are?!
Drop it! This is not the time
to be fighting.
Ah?
What's your problem?
Are you one of his friends?
It's not that I am his friend...
Though I am a draker too...
What are you saying, bastard?
Are you saying it's that lil' puny ship
of yours who caught it?
I'm not saying anything like that...
It doesn't look good...
The city of Quon is a very
important place as a base for drakers.
I don't want them to hold a grudge
against us.
No, rather than that...
If things remain like this,
no one here will buy this dragon.
Bunch of idiots!
Ah! Captain!
Why are you causing problems
to these people?!
Are you sure you can walk like that?
If you can worry about that...
Don't go causing unnecesary problems,
you damn spineless rubble!
If you have energy to pick fights
you'd better use it to pick debris instead!
But... that's not the...
I don't give a damn
about your excuses!
I see that dealing with incompetent
crew looks the same wherever you go.
Yeah, there are people like that.
-Ah? And you're one of them!
-Oh?!
Hey, what do you mean?!
Confirmed incompetent!
Listen!
If it was not for this boy,
you'd probably all be dead by now.
If another heat ray went off...
The destruction wouldn't have ended here.
But... the damages are so serious...
-Gibbs-san.
-Mmm?
Let's donate the dragon to the city.
Ah?
Huh?
Lee-san, what the hell are you saying?!
Besides the damages to the city
being so serious...
If we were to take advantage of the situation
and profit, it's the same as asking for a rebellion.
The real good deal for us is...
To trade the dragon in exchange for
ship repairs and the rest of the expenses.
Wait, wait, wait!
Do you not see how difficult was
for us to take that dragon down?!
You won't see a single coin
if we can't sell it.
Ah... I wonder what Crocco
would say if he knew this...
I don't mind...
Crocco!
As long as they repair our
ship, I don't mind.
Well, that's settled.
Ah... not much we can do
about it after all.
Ahhh... what a waste of effort...
Let's call it even for both of us, okay?
Ah! It better be enough food
for me after this!
Ah...
All this bleeding made me hungry.
I think losing blood has nothing to do
with being hungry...
I will be at Gramps Ura's place
eating some meat.
Okay! We are going to clean up
the city too, Mika!
Ugh... let me go!
I'm injured, goddamnit!
This isn't the strength of
an injured man, is it?
Let me go I tell you!
-Shut your mouth and come!
-As pleasant as always...
Mmmm... I think he'll be fine.
Good grief... they are always
causing problems.
Yes, they are your friends
after all, Jiro.
Of course!
They're a good bunch.
Listen...
Katja, I'm sorry.
Mmm?
The festival...
We pretty much ruined it.
Even after I promised you
we'd come together.
Ah... sorry.
Your face was so serious,
I couldn't hold my laugh!
Eh?!
Ah...
-But...
-Mmm?
I sure wanted to see...
The moment you hunted
the dragon, Jiro.
♪〜
Translation: TomoyaNC   Proofreading: akemilena