What a nice wind...
Yeah...
Damn it... Nice days like this
make you wish you didn't have to work...
Come on, what are you saying,
deputy captain?
If you're like that who's gonna
set an example here?
Say, Gibbs, how long it's been
since you came to this ship?
Eh? Let's see...
About 8 years.
That's a lot.
I guess this lifestyle was perfect for you.
Seems so.
For me, it's been 3 years
since I became deputy captain.
Why don't you just call it captain
at this point?
It's "deputy" for a reason.
I can't just simply drop it.
Capella, how's things?
Very good!
The clouds are calm too.
Since we have a tailwind,
we might arrive to Quon town
in 3 days if it continues like this.
Yeah, I'm leaving it to you.
We'll finally be able to refuel!
These days have been pretty rough
for the ship after all,
she's run-down.
We gotta fix her up everywhere, right?
Quon is a big town,
so take the chance to relax
as much as you want.
Yay!
My shoulders have been so stiff lately...!
I'll find a good massage shop.
Ah, Crocco-san do you know any?
Wha? How would I know.
I can't believe what I've been
listening you say!
-Huh?
-Since the latest departure
we haven't captured almost any dragon!
We did catch a few though?
We're a large crew here.
With just that we're so deep in the red
it's almost purple!
Refueling and reparations
are not cheap in the slightest, you know?
Do you understand what I mean, right,
deputy captain?
I guess...
Here!
Oof...
There...
Yoshi-san...
Do we have to peel all these today?
These are sprouting already!
We gotta take them all out, right...
In order to maintain a draking vessel,
we need a huge amount of money.
Dragons are sold for a large sum,
so as long as we capture them
we can cover the costs...
But when we don't...
We are the ones who have to starve...
Ah! Hey!
♪〜
〜♪
I'm... so tired of potatoes...
And food's about the only thing
to look forward too...
I do wish I could prepare you
something else, really...
I won't allow it. The problem is that
you always are wasting money.
But we do have dragons that we captured!
Those are for sale.
No one will notice if we take a bit...
Oh, okay, shall I deduct it
from your salary then?
Ah... I'm sorry.
We'll arrive to a big town soon, won't we?
We just need to be a little patient!
Takita...
I'm sick of this...
Meat... let me eat dragon meat...
Don't be selfish.
Here, eat some more!
Damn...
I'm gonna sleep the next 3 days off.
Please do your work!
You...
What is it?
Nothing...
Well, nothing we can do!
When we finish the delivery,
we'll have some time off.
Yeah! I can get as many hangovers
as I want!
I want to sleep in a big bed!
Yeah!
No more sweaty beds for a while!
And... Right, Jiro...
You're looking forward to it too, huh?
Huh? What?
Don't play dumb.
If you're to become a full-fledged
man of the crew...
You need to know what a woman is...
Eh?!
Can't you talk about that when
there's no girls around...?
-Jiro-san!
-Stop already!
I don't even need to say that
you're paying yourselves.
Jiro!
Stupid, stupid... stupid!
Before we arrive to the town...
It would be great if we managed
to catch another one...
You're right.
Hm?
What's wrong?
Look at that!
Look, that flag signal...
An SOS!
Ah... guys, do you hear me?
What's the matter, Vadakin?
Sorry to interrupt while you're eating
but it's an emergency, look behind the ship.
Oh dear...
Bring the ship closer immediately!
Of all things...
I'll approach it.
It's an ocean cargo ship.
Going down!
I wonder if it's a shipwreck...?
If it is, I hope they're alive...
There we go.
Looks like a pretty old ship.
Doesn't feel like there's anyone.
Maybe we were too late...
Great! Then let's split up
and investigate!
Sounds good.
Then, Vannie and me will go inside...
Hey, I'm raising them!
Eh? Ah...
-I'll go down to check.
-Yes.
Faye and Soraya go check the crew room.
-Yes ma'am!
-Eh?
Ehhh?!
C'mon, Soraya, let's go.
As empty as an abandoned shell.
Let's look all the way to the back.
What?
I'm so hungry...
I even said I wouldn't work anymore...
What are you talking about?
There's no one here.
If there are no bodies,
does that mean someone rescued them already?
Oh?
There's a lot of old books!
How nice...
Oh! Maybe we can sell them in the town!
Hey, we're not thieves!
I'll just borrow this poetry anthology.
Damn this ship, it was a false alarm.
Ouch!
Oww, that hurts...
Ow, ow...
Soraya!
What are you doing?
It seems the floor was rotten!
How was over there?
No problem.
I see a problem!
It hurts...
Then, let's take down that flag
and go back.
If they got rescued they could have
taken it down.
It just makes it confusing.
Right... it never rains but it pours...
An airship?
Ah!
Gibbs! Pull us up, quick!
What happens?
A ship is approaching!
A ship?
Okay! I'll lower the hooks!
Is there something wrong with that ship?
I have a bad feeling about it.
Pull them up quickly!
They're chasing us.
That outline...
Ah, Jiro-san!
I'll watch from above!
Rise at full speed, 10 to starboard.
Yes!
So the rescue ship was just a bait...
Shit!
They're faster than us!
Vanabelle's bad feeling was right.
For real?
They're air pirates.
Boy, we're so lucky a draking vessel
fell for it!
They probably have dragon oil onboard.
Nice steering they've got there.
But I won't let you escape.
They're catching up!
I don't want to use more fuel
for mere pirates, but...
It's the same as always...
Okay, let's go!
Their helmsman is very good!
Ahh! Our run-down ship is getting
even more run-down...!
Hey!
This is not the time to say that!
Takita! Crouch down!
Ugh... why?
Idiot! Don't stand there dumbfounded!
I'm sorry!
Hey... your eyelid...
I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
Takita!
How dare they...
They don't even care for women
and children?!
Everyone, go inside! Quick!
You bastard...!
When I shoot one, ten come back...
We can't fight a machine gun with
single shot guns!
Bridge! We're at a disadvantage
in this position.
At least raise the ship over them!
We know!
We gotta do it, then!
Jiro here! I arrived to the lookout.
They plan to board our ship!
What?! Tsk...
A kite?!
They intend to board us from
the lookout.
This is bad...
Jiro! Get out of there!
Vanabelle, cover me when I go out.
What are you going to do?
I'm gonna board them instead.
Mika...
Mika!
Eh?!
Mika-san!
Oh, no...
Eh... Mika?!
Ah?
This thing isn't made to aim for
small targets...
Niko!
What did you say about small targets?
Hey! What are you waiting for?
Board them already!
You guys! Are you ready?
Ah? What's he...?
Ah!! Wait, you!
Wha- He's acting on his own again!
Why are you surprised?
Ah- Eh, wha?!
No way, no way, no waaaay!
That's dangerous!
He boarded us alone!
Is he sane?
Don't flinch! Shoot him!
Don't move!
Ouch...
Put your hands up and kneel down!
Hurry up!
Mika-san!
Mika!
Tsk...
This is bad...
-Mika!
-Mika...
Ow, it hurts...
You're pretty good, huh...
Look what you did, you ruined
my pretty face...
I'll leave your face full of holes too!
Be grateful.
Ah... F-freeze...!
Hey! Can't you see the gun?
Sto-...
Bullshit...
I've never seen someone who'd
board a pirate ship alone...
Never in my life!
Who on earth are you?
Just a draker.
Owww...
Hey.
Do you have meat?
What? Meat?
Yeah, meat.
Ohh!
You eat surprisingly well, huh?
I'll give you as much as you want,
but get out of here...
What's this bundle?
We happened to get some
good dragon meat...
Oh!
"Lean dragon meat pastrami, pirate-style"
You're making the spices work really well!
The fragance is great too.
This smoked meat looks really good...
What kind of dish is this?
Pa... Pastrami!
It's our family's secret recipe
that uses a special spice blend!
I see!
And our special spice blend is
clove, cinnamon, and nutmeg
all mixed together, you see.
It's a high-class item,
also called allspice!
Savour it thoroughly!
Delicious!
Eh?
Shit, it jammed at the worst moment!
I lowered my guard because I was hungry.
You were hiding there, huh?
You're the one who shot at Takita, right?
Y... Yes...
Ah! Mika-san!
Hey.
Mika! Are you okay?
They said they'd share food with us.
Eh?
What's going on?
He suppressed it all by himself.
He's messed up.
That's just how he is.
I don't know who are
the pirates anymore.
Mika-san?
Looks good.
Ah! A dragon!
Above the clouds! It's inside the sun!
Ohh! It looks pretty voluminous too!
We'll leave as soon as Mika's up!
Jiro, don't lose sight of it!
Everyone, to your positions!
For the love of god, please catch it!
If you let it go, I won't be able
to pay your salaries!
They were... amazing...
Yeah... they're something else...
Drakers... huh...
He looks so happy.
♪〜
Translation: akemilena   Proofreading: TomoyaNC