-It's coming!
-Grab onto something!
Yeah!
Damn... it's too strong!
We're being pulled!
So stubborn...
Tell the bridge
to get it closer!
Bring it until it's 10 meters close!
Easier said than done!
Now! Pull!
Takita! Bring the bullets over here!
Yes...!
What are you doing?!
Right! Sorry!
It's coming.
Bomb lance, ready!
-Yeah!
-Yes!
Ah...
Here it comes...!
Fire!!
If it hides behind the clouds again
it's going to be troublesome...
Yeah...
Also...
If it goes too wild,
the meat's taste will get worse.
Mika!
He's going on his own again...
Looks good.
That bastard...
That was quite scary...
-Mika finished it!
-Lower the hook!
If you don't get moving it's gonna sink!
Mika! Are you okay?
Come on, Takita,
don't stay there astonished.
This is... dragon hunting...
Mika!
Jumping onto a dragon that still
had some strength left is too reckless!
I hate bomb lances.
What?
Chasing dragons that swim through the sky,
To the west, east, south and north.
Nowadays, there aren't much left.
Draking vessel on service: Quin Zaza.
Dissecting the dragons they capture,
and selling them during their travels.
They don't have a port to go home to.
Catching the wind, seizing the shadows,
their journey goes on.
♪〜
〜♪
The hoist machine is ready!
We're ready here too.
Stop!
Mmmm...
Hm?
It's pretty good.
It doesn't have many wounds too, nice.
This is gonna sell for quite a lot.
Our ship sure is full of holes though...
It was about to fall apart!
Come on, don't get so angry.
Geez...
Honestly, what do they think a ship is?!
Get number 12!
Please be careful with that
so it doesn't get any scratch!
This is for large trading auctions.
Retail is over there!
Welcome! How much do you need?
Fill me this with oil.
Sure thing.
Our oil is extracted from the skin
right after we capture it.
You can use it for cooking too.
-And today's smells especially well!
-Oh my!
How about some meat too?
If you can't eat it all,
you can pickle it in salt or smoke it
and it will last for a while!
Then, I will take some.
Sure!
Very good, very good.
Takita, don't you think you're
better suited for this?
But with just this, I won't be able
to get into the ship, right?
I'm gonna do my best!
Do you have dragon liver?
I heard it works for night blindness.
Of course we do!
Takita.
Yes!
Ah! Mika-san, you can't!
Hm?
Skipping out and snitching foo...
I'm not snitching food.
I was just scraping the meet that was
stuck on the bone.
It would be a waste, right?
Chop logic...
-Wha?
-Nothing!
Anyway, fresh dragon meat
tastes good even raw!
Hey, Takita!
Don't go snithing food when you're just a newbie!
No, it's not it, it's just that Mika-san...!
-Aaah, I'm so so busy...
-Ah!
Miiiikaaa!!
Out of the question.
60% for us. Nothing less.
If you're not satisfied then this deal is off.
There's also a limit to the amount of
booze we can put on board...
That's the only thing I envy from the surface.
To begin with, it's always you
who's doing whatever you want!
Takita, don't learn anything from him, okay?
What? No roof for us?
Can't believe there isn't a single room avaliable.
Can't the women at least?
Sir, I'm so sorry...
We've been on the ship for a long while.
I wanted the crew to get a good rest...
You see, the townspeople are scared...
You know what they say, when a draking vessel
stops in a town, a dragon will fall on it.
How ill omened...
That's just a superstition!
-Jiro.
-It's the opposite.
Draking vessels go around places
where dragons appear.
Precisely because we take down dragons
We can prevent damage before it happens!
We don't need your pretentious talk!
You aren't even registered in the association,
just an unlicensed ship!
We can't trust you all the more!
We aren't really welcome here...
Nothing we can do.
We're strangers no matter where we go.
Vannie-san...
We're letting you do business here
without kicking you out.
Isn't that more than enough?
But we're...!
Understood.
Well, sorry for imposing on you!
We're more than used to living in the ship,
so don't mind.
We'll get you the necessary supplies.
Sure, thanks a bunch.
Once you're done you better get out of here quick.
Gibbs...
Don't say anything, Jiro.
You can't say we are respectable even as flattery.
You're too earnest.
They'll buy the meat and oil of the dragon we captured
but they won't let us into the town...
I don't get it.
It's not reasonable, any of it.
Ah-ah...
And here I hoped I could sleep
sprawled for once...
I want to take a bath too.
Eh, what, Mika-san...
What do you pretend?
I just wondered if you smelled.
Eeh?!
What were you thinking?!
Takita, you can sleep anywhere as long
as you have a pillow, am I wrong?
No can do!
We aren't made as sturdy as you are.
A-and then...?
Was I... smelly?
Hm... you smelled like a person.
By the way, what are you doing?
When did you start a fire...
I got hungry after work, you see?
A grill?
As long as there's straw and charcoal,
open fire is good too,
but this is pine for the oil mill
and it has a lot of resin.
Also, judging from how it tasted raw,
I thought it'd be really good as steak.
Mika-san always looks absent-minded,
but when it comes to food
he gets really talkative.
Creepy, right?
Slice this rock-hard bread...
Ah... it's hard...
Spread the dragon's fat on the iron plate...
Ah! This smell...
When it's done on both sides,
a splash of grappa...
Slice the steak and put it between bread...
And it's done!
That's...
That's gotta be delicious...
-Hm?
-Ah!
You're monopolizing it?!
That's big enough to share it with everyone...
Mika! Give me some!
For me too!
If you eat that much now
you won't be able to eat dinner!
I helped you start the fire, give me my share!
-Exactly!
-My share!
Heeeey!
Eh?
A dragon... a dragon appeared
above the neighbour town! I just got a call!
There were more aside from that one?
Well, what a bummer...
Please!
Hey! It's your job, isn't it?
Go exterminate it!
Even if you tell us to go now...
We just finished dissecting one,
and we haven't refueled either.
You don't need to worry that much,
they rarely attack people directly.
And it's not like the dragon
will fall on the town for sure...
My wife and daughter are in that town!
It'll be too late after it happens...
But...
That's why you hunters are for!
You're only saying what's convenient for you!
Let's go.
Mika! We haven't even refueled!
It's just the neighbouring town, right?
We don't need to.
We'll go, capture it, and come back.
Like we always do.
If there's a dragon, we have to work.
It's just that.
Well, yeah.
Niko, put out the fire of the oiling pot
and put on a lid.
Sure thing!
Takita! Go tell the bridge
to get ready for takeoff.
Ah... yes!
Hey! We're turning it on soon!
Sure sure!
Upsy...
-Shall we?
-Yes!
Jiro and Vannie go call those who are resting!
Jiro, time to work.
I know.
Ah, but you know,
Thinking that we gotta sleep
in a small cabin after getting back...
It's not really worth it...
Of... of course we'll prepare a place
to sleep, a bath,
Food and drink too!
Great!
Once we get everyone,
we're untying the mooring line!
Leave the cargo on the surface!
Got it!
I wonder how is it this time...
It's exactly above the town of all things!
It's bigger than the one we got this morning!
Something is off...
the atmosphere feels tense.
Gibbs, look.
Look how it's rising its plumes.
It's calling its friends.
Really?
Yeah, probably.
I feel it.
Probably...?
When it comes to dragons,
what he says is never wrong.
Are you saying there are more around?
No good, it's not reacting to flash bombs.
It better not be doing it on purpose
knowing we can't
do anything if it's above the town.
No way...
We gotta hurry up.
If another one shows up we're done for.
Wha...
Mika!
Hey, Mika!
What are you gonna do if it starts rampaging?!
-I'll think about that when it happens.
-Mika!
Wh... What?!
For now... we don't have to worry about
the town anymore.
Eh?
Get up, hurry.
Now it suddenly got aggresive, huh?
It's as if it was angry with us...
Boss! You okay?
Jiro,
bring as many bomb lances as you find!
Okay!
"It looks angry" you say...
It's exactly that.
Eh?
It smells the same as the one
we took down today.
That means...
Probably, this one's the mother.
It seems it noticed too.
It's angry because we ate her child.
Then, the one it was calling...
What?
No... I know this is being too soft but...
I feel a bit bad for her...
Takita.
Aren't you misunderstanding
what hunters are?
Dragons aren't something
that just wait to be hunted.
People who are not ready to kill,
will die.
-Crocco-san!
-Ah?
The ship's not going to last!
We can't have it rampaging over the town!
Shit!
Boss.
Let's cute the anchor's rope
and shake it off!
We need to reposition ourselves.
No, we can't be sure
it won't go back to the town.
If the ship sinks it
will all be for nothing!
Niko!
Mika!
Can't you save me a bit more gently...?
This one'll be hanging on for dear life
until it runs out of strength.
We can't possibly shake it off.
We'll finish it as is!
How many bullets did we shoot?
Doesn't this thing feel any pain?
Dammit!
I don't really feel any reaction.
Takita! Bring me a stun lance.
Y... yes!
Don't.
If you use that, the taste gets worse.
Eh?
If we're gonna bring it down, we gotta do it
as delicious as we can.
You think this is the moment to say that?!
Fine, cover me with a gun!
-I'll go too!
-Ah- hey, Jiro!
Go!
Yeah!
You gonna eat me?
Oh no!
Crocco-san!
I don't care what you do, but raise the ship!
Vannie!
Mika!!
Mika-san, that!
Mika-san!
-Don't let it go, Jiro!
-The hook, quick!
Yes! Ah...
Stun lance...
I ended up using it...
Time to eat.
So good!
When was the last time we ate such a feast?
-One more bottle, please.
-Eh?
Vannie, don't drink too much.
I only have opened 3 bottles.
Eh? When did you...?!
That one's the last, okay?
Ugh, I can't eat more.
This is bliss...
Man, so sloppy.
Wha?
This is so good...
These days
we only had salted meat stew to eat...
Right.
Well, excuse me.
Ah... No, no!
We're not saying your cooking is bad,
Yoshi-san!
Here, Mika, since I had the chance.
I borrowed the restaurant's kitchen
and roasted it but...
You used a stun lance, right?
I wonder how's the taste.
With dragons, you don't know until you eat it.
How is it?
-Good...
-Yeah, you're lying.
Takita, you're a newbie,
I don't want to see you yawning!
I can't control a yawn...
I'm not a morning person...
And it's so cold...
If you're like that,
you're gonna let dragons escape.
Dragons are early to bed early to rise.
Really?
Yeah...
probably.
Ever since countries started to aim for the sky
pursuing the rare dragons
it's been about half a century.
Nowadays, there aren't much left.
Draking vessel on service: Quin Zaza.
Pursuing their meat, oil and entrails,
and sometimes the bounty they have on them.
Chasing the dragons that swim through the sky and air.
They don't have a port to go home to.
Catching the wind, seizing the shadows,
their journey goes on.
♪〜
〜♪