♪〜
〜♪
Ow!
I can't tell if we're in a draking vessel
or riding a wild horse...
I hope we don't bump into anything...
That's if we don't end up
in pieces first...
You think Takita will be able
to reach this hell of a place?
We don't have any other place to search,
we can only hope she's there.
We're reaching our limit here too!
Time's up.
We know already!
Attention, crew...
The 48 hours of emergency search
have come to an end.
Though it pains our heart...
all activities regarding the search
are suspended as of now.
Shit!
We didn't savour that dragon yet.
What's wrong?
Mika-san!!
Mika-saan!!
Bridge! Starboard and straight away!
At those pointy rocks!
Capella!
Right! Going full starboard!
Takita...
Is this for real?!
What?!
The wind has carried her voice here!
What do we do now?
We cannot remain static
with this wind!
Move our right horizontal tail
as closer to the rocks as possible!
Vanabelle! Support the bridge
in my place!
Yes, leave it to me.
Move it slowly.
The altitude is fine,
10 degrees to our right!
Miikaaa-saaan!!
Miiiikaaa-saaaan!!
Miiikaaa-saaan!!
Takita!! Jump!!
Mika-san!
Takita... You were alive as I thought.
Luck's about the only thing
I have going for me.
Takita!!
Ascella-san!
Thank you very, very much
for taking care of me!!
I won't forget you
for as long as I live!
If you're that lucky, I'm sure
we will meet again!
So that was the famous "Mika-san"...
You're a draker, don't fall
off like that ever again!
Mmm?
By the way, that little thing
on your back...
Ah...
It's the cub of the dragon that
fell with me...
Eh...
I haven't tasted a dragon cub
in my life!
Don't eat it!
Wai-!
Wipe off your drool!
Wai- The wind's spreading it
at my fac-
Ew! So dirty...
Wait, Mika-san...! Ugh...
Takita...
Vannie-san!
I'm sorry I worried you...
Thank god.
It seems that this is the place
that "ferry" was aiming for.
Vannie-san, Mika-san,
can I count on you to help me
without asking any questions?
I'm returning this little one
to the pod!
Wha?
Are you... the real Takita?
I know it already!
I smell bad! I'm aware of it!
So... you're the real deal.
Everyone, I'm sorry I worried you all!
It's me, Takita!
I'm home again!
It- It's her voice!
Takita!
Do you even know how many
problems have you caused to us all?!
Takita! I'm glad you were safe.
I believed she was alright
from the beginning!
Are you okay?!
Any wounds?!
As serious as ever, eh?
Just let it slide this one time, okay?
Yes...
I am... completely fine!
I'm so glad she's back!
I hope she isn't a ghost...
That girl...
is one hell of a girl alright!
This has been harder than
chasing dragons!
You can say that.
I'm so glad she's fine...
Thank you, really.
But... I didn't specially...
The wind has calmed down.
Eh! They're gonna leaving this
one behind!
What should I do...?
Ah... right there!
It's a different dragon!
Ah! They're gonna hunt down
that pod!
Oh!
Dragons preying on each other!
What a rare sight!
Takita!
Tell everyone to follow
that dragon.
Eh?
If we do that, we will get closer
to that pod.
Crocco-san!
There's a different type of dragon
that has appeared to hunt down that pod!
Ah?
That type...! It's a real rarity!
I'm sure they'd sell well.
Ah? You mean to hunt them?
We came here to do that
in the first place, right?
You heard it already! Let's do this!
You heard the bridge, guys!
Takita has come back and she brought
extra dragons with her!
We sure can't get bored with
her around us!
You're damn right! What a
spunky girl!
I'm dead tired though...
We're leaving the emotional reunion
for after this!
One last work before the celebration!
Bring all your strenght and let's do this!
We're going to raise our altitude even more!
Engine room, how's things?
Can we bear it?
What? Are you serious?!
We've been forcing it pretty
bad already...
Besides that, you should be worrying
about the hull more than the engine.
Ahh? As long as we don't bump into
anything we'll be fine!
Eh?!!
Crocco-san! Don't speak as if this
hasn't anything to do with you!
We're running out of oxygen
and the engine is knocking nonstop!
Then we should change the fuel.
Hiro, hurry up!
Ah... she's treating us like slaves...
We're entering the clouds!
All hands on deck!
Yes, sir!
I'll be on port side!
Okay, we'll be on starboard then!
Understood!
We have poor visibility,
be careful!
Takita!
Jiro-san!
Takita, you're hurt, aren't you?!
Don't be wandering around here!
If you were to fall again, then what?!
Go inside and rest.
Y-yes!
Amazing...
Dragons... attacking other dragons.
Gibbs...
Mika!
Those dragons are focused on the pod.
The moment they have their jaws
busy, shoot them.
I know that!
Nice!
Uwah! What's with this number?!
Where are they coming from?!
They seem like moths
gathering at a light.
So this is the so called
dragon corridor...
I cannot believe my eyes!
Hey, are you kidding?
If something like this exists...
Why do we have to fly around the
world searching for them?!
Yeah...
But a dragon corridor is
a very strange phenomenon.
You can only see one every few years
and they always appear suddenly.
You can't predict something like that, right?
Soraya, I think you should study
even if it's only a little.
When the smoke blows,
dragons will pass by...
So that's what it means.
With this situation, I can't even
think of a way to return this little one!
Sorry, sorry...
He- hey!
Now we're alone, you and I, eh?!
Hurry up with that anchor!
Keep moving!
We're finished here!
Good! Let's hurry up and go back!
Hey, over there... something is coming!
Tha- that's stupidly big...!
I haven't seen one like that in my life!
The group that is anchoring, hurry up
and get them back in the ship now!
It's coming this way!
Full starboard, hurry!
Jaw dropping...
I guess it saw this feast going on and
came down from the upper layers.
Bridge!
Yes, we understand!
I'll take on the elevator!
We're retreating away from this place, now!
There's a strong wind blowing towards north!
I'll go around and
ride the airflow!
Ah! That's...
Coming at us...
It's riding the same wind!
Mika-san! What happened?
There's a huge dragon that
none of us have seen before!
I'm gonna hunt it!
Ah, Mika-san!
Ow...
Everyone on the ship yet?
We're retreating!
-Takita.
-Vannie-san.
If you're a draker too...
Eh?
Do your duty as one of us!
And what will you do, Vannie-san?
I can't leave that idiot alone!
Oh... what the hell are you doing?!
Hey, wait! Hey!
Come with me!
Damn it...
What a day...
Hiro-san, I've been looking for you!
Eh?
Is the autogyro able to fly now?
Huh?
What are you saying all of a sudden...?
Please, I beg you!
Eh? Ah...
But... you see...
I have to return this little one
no matter what!
I'll prepare the high altitude fuel for you...
But, whatever happens...
Ah, what are you doing?
It's dangerous out here!
Eh?
I'm launching you for real!
Are you really sure?!
Yes, no problem!
Huh? I see a lot of problems with this!
Damnit... Why are you always
causing issues, Takita?!
This fuel sometimes gets air into the motor
so it can be a bit difficult to accelerate.
Eh? Ah... okay.
Don't you dare... fall off!
Ye-...
Yes!
There you go!
Hey! Don't shake it like that!
Well... let's get back to work!
Listen... what's that?
Ah! What the hell are they doing?!
Ah, Jiro-san! Over there!
Damnit... Why am I doing this?
Ah... Vanabelle!
What do you think you're doing,
goddamnit?!
You're hunting it, aren't you?
Yeah, it'll be so tasty...
Takita, why are you doing this?
Because I'm... I'm a draker.
Huh?!
I killed this little one's mother
and ate it.
You're a draker, of course you'd do that.
Yes.
We're... a dragon and a draker.
Huh?
That's why I have to return
this little one to its pod...
so it can become a full-fledged dragon!
Full-fledged?
What are you saying...?
I don't get you.
I want...
I also want to live in the sky.
I think... I got it.
You... you said to charge it with
extra power after all...
We kinda overdid it...
But that explosion was the best, right?!
Niko!
By a hair's breadth...
With this, my debt is settled.
Takita! Go!!
The next time we see each other...
I'm definetely going to hunt you.
Because I'm a draker after all.
That's why... till then...
Don't let anyone eat you, okay?
You'll be fine.
Here we go!
'Sup.
Takita! Jiro!
What the hell were you thinking
to do this now of all times?!
Hiro, you too!
And you too, Mika!
You're always like this...
-Worrying all of us...
-In the end
-Think about what you're doing for once!
-I missed the last shot...
The sunrise...
We can barely see the pod now...
Yeah.
Mika-san
The sky is so big and wide.
Ah?
Hey, guys!
You seem alright!
You must be hungry, right?
Hurry up inside, I'm gonna prep
breakfast soon!
One steak for me!
But it's early in the morning.
When you pull an all nighter,
no one cares about that!
Then, the same goes for booze.
Takita's back and all!
We gotta celebrate!!
I should've taken a bite off of that
one when I got the chance...
Hey...
Don't laugh at me! Please!
Geez!
Chasing dragons that swim through the sky,
To the west, east, south and north.
Catching the wind, seizing the shadows,
our journey goes on.
Hey, Takita! Bring the explosives!
Right away!
Takita, what are you doing?
Bring here the bomb lances!
Coming!
It looks delicious... Right?
Yeah...
Please, be careful!
Hey, Takita! Come here!
Ah, coming!
♪〜
Translation: TomoyaNC   Proofreading: akemilena